靠近点
Come in close.
再近点
Closer.
正因为 越是你认为自己看到了
Because the more you think you see,
就越容易瞒过你的双眼
the easier it'll be to fool you.
也因为 被看得到的
Because what is seeing?
你正在看的 其实只是你的眼睛在过滤信息
You're looking,but what you're really doing is filtering,interpreting,
并解释 传递给你的大脑
searching for meaning.
而我的工作
My job?
就是笑纳你们所赐予我的礼物 你们的注意力
To take that most precious of gifts you give me,your attention,
然后用其欺骗你们的双眼
and use it against you.
(芝加哥 星期一)
现在我开始快速翻动这叠牌堆
I'm going to flip through this deck.
我需要你看到一张牌
And I want you to see one card.
当然不是这张 如果是这张就太明显了
Not this one. That's too obvious.
请仔细注意观察
Pay close attention.
刚太快了 我再来一次
That was too fast. I'll do it again.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
好了
Okay.
- 现在看到一张牌了吗 - 看到了
- Now did you see one? - Yes.
- 记住了吗 - 记住了
- Do you have one in mind? - Yes.
现在 在这堆里能找到你刚才看的到牌吗
Now,do you see your card here?
没有
No.
那是因为你看的时候站得太近了
That's because you're looking too closely.
我整晚都在告诉你们
And what have I been telling you all night?
站的越近…
The closer you look...
你的视野越狭隘
The less you see.
(新奥尔良 星期二)
现在 看着我的双眼
Now look into my eyes.
然后 睡着吧 很好
And sleep. Okay.
然后
And...
如果你能够到这张钞票 那它就归你了
If you can get this bill from me,you can have it.
来吧 拿走啊 别客气
Go ahead. Take it. Get it.
或者你说出你的名字 你也可以拿走它
If you can say your name,you can have it.
好了 你可以不用动了 在原地站一会儿吧
All right,just hang out there,wriggle a sec.
我现在呢 准备偷窥一下
I'm gonna take a little peek under the hood
- 你老公的大脑 - 原来是这样的 我的天…
- of your hubby's brain. - Oh,no,no,no.
我看到了一幅画面…
I'm picturing...
- 千万别告诉我你在想什么 - 那肯定的
- Don't tell me. - Of course.
沙滩 鸡尾酒…
Beach. Cocktails.
佛罗里达州
Florida?
听着 那是出差 别想歪了
Look,it was a business trip.
我是说 算是出差吧
I mean,it is a kind of business.
是啊 思想上"出差"
Maybe the oldest business.
你瞎说"小可爱"我们走…
You know what,Honey Bee,let's...
她动不了的 老兄
She can't move,Mack.
你现在在想一个女人的名字
You're thinking of a woman's name.
开头字母是 A B C
A! B! C!
D E F G
H I J…
H,I,J...
J 珍 简 珍妮特
J? Jean. Jane. Janet.
谁是珍妮特
Who's Janet?
你认识珍妮特吗
You know Janet?
原来是你最好的朋友啊 我猜对了吧
It's not your best friend,is it?
- 你妹妹 - 求你别这样
- Your sister? - No,please.
是她妹妹啊 我的天呐
Her sister? Oh,my God.
你不是去出差了
You weren't away on business.
- 你是去上珍妮特了 - 我没有
- You were away on Janet. - No.
那可是你老婆的妹妹
Your wife's sister!
好吧 我们还是站过来点
Okay,we need to move over here,
因为现在你老婆看起来有点不开心
because it seems like she's a little bit upset right now.
你想解决这个事情吗
You want this to go away?
- 那当然 - 好 把你钱包掏出来
- Yes. - Okay,pull out your wallet.
别磨叽了 拿出来吧
Come on,get it out.
你也是这样勒索其他人的吗
Do you shake down everybody like this?
不 就比较特殊的几个人
No,only the special few.
瞧瞧这里 200美元很公平吧
What is this? Two hundred seem fair?
你知道吗 这个事情看起来很严重 我们还是收250美元吧
You know what? This is a big deal. Let's go $250.
您打劫真有艺术感
You're a stick-up artist.
是啊 那必须的
Yeah. Of course.
好了 继续沉睡
Okay,and sleep!
现在 当我打一下响指
Now,when I snap my fingers,
你就什么都不记得了
you won't remember any of this.
还有你 沃伦 贝提
And you,Warren Beatty,
每当你看到 甚至想起珍妮特
every time you see or even think of Janet,
你的脑海里就浮现出我的裸体
you're gonna picture me naked.
那可不会是什么好看的"景色"了
And that's not a pretty sight.
我知道了
Yeah.
好了 你完全清醒了
And... You're wide awake!
好了 我们已经尽力了
Well,we did the best we could,
只不过有的人天生就无法被催眠
but some people just aren't to be hypnotized.
- 是吗 是不是我哪里做错了 - 该走了 宝贝
- I did it wrong? - Come on,Honey Bee.
- 当然没有 你做的完全正确 - 来 给你买晚餐吃
- Oh,no,you did it fine. - Let me buy you dinner.
照顾好她哦
Look after her.
不过得先去取点钱
Just have to hit an ATM first.
(纽约 星期三)
女士们先生们 我是下一个最有名的魔术师
Ladies and gentlemen,I am the next great magician,
如果有谁能识破我的把戏
and I will give $100
我就给他100美元
to anyone who can tell me how this trick is done.
我在布鲁克林 就这个城市的梅尔熟食店拿了把普通勺子
I have an ordinary spoon from Mel's Deli,right here in Brooklyn.
检查一下
Check it out.
好 现在请各位非常认真的看好了
Now,everyone please pay very,very close attention.
因为我会用我的意念把这个勺子折弯
Because I'm about to bend this spoon with my mind.
谢谢 谢谢各位 递给大家看看
Thank you. Thank you. Pass that around.
- 这是什么 - 你想干什么
- What's this? - What are you doing,man?
瞧瞧这里好像这是一个勺子和一个杆子
Look at this! Looks like we got a spoon and a stem.
我还能识破其他把戏呢
I've got other tricks.
或者给我100美元就算了
Or you could give me my 100 bucks.
你说你要给的哦
You said you would.
钱包挺好看的
Nice wallet.
这位先生 你眼力不错
You have a very good eye,sir.
谢谢
Thanks.
糟了 钱包
Wallet.
钱包 手表
My wallet. My watch!
抓小偷啊
Stop that guy!
就是那个穿皮夹克的
Stop that guy in the leather jacket!
他偷了我钱包
He's got my wallet!
(洛杉矶 星期四)
你们好 洛杉矶的观众们
Okay,Los Angeles,
准备好 见证奇蹟的时刻了吗
are we ready to end this thing?
非常好
Yeah!
当那个计时器清零的时候
When that timer hits zero,
一满满水箱的食人鱼
a tank full of flesh-eating piranhas
就会从上面掉下来
will fall from above.
一位女士被考起来关在里面 仔细看好了
A lady has to have handcuffs. Right,girls?
一 二 三
One,two,three!
快帮忙 停下来啊
Help! Stop it!
她好像是真的逃不出来了
She's serious! She can't get out!
快找人帮忙
Go get some help!
哥们快救人
Help,dude!
快让开 让开
Get out of the way! Move! Move!
别沮丧啊 这太简单了
Come on! This is bullshit!
刚有谁觉得会失败啊
Whoever thought of this is a sick sadist!
我可是你的终极粉丝
I am your biggest fan.
看你吻的这么深情 我就知道了
I could tell by the way you're attacking my face right now.
关门先 隔墙有耳
Close the door. Bad apartment building.
- 魔术师 过来呀 - 好的
- Magician,come here. - Okay.
- 等等 等等 - 什么
- Wait,wait. - What? What?
你是怎么办到的…
How did you do that...
你是说刚塔上的7个菱形
The seven of diamonds on the side of the tower?
- 是啊 - 那可是机密
- Yes. - That's a trade secret.
我给你个提示 贿赂一下塔里的电工就好了
I'll give you a hint. It involved bribing the tower electrician.
多少钱
How much?
50块
50 bucks.
- 但是那也好难啊 - 当然 谢谢
- But it's so hard. - Oh,thank you.
一般都是7吗
Is it always a seven?
我可以用52种不同的方式来变那个魔术
I could do that trick 52 different ways.
那你能在我身上变52个魔术嘛
Can you do 52 different tricks on me?
我尽量看我能干点什么吧
I'll see what I can do.
神秘的男人
Magic man!
我喜欢你的沐浴露味道
I love your shampoo.
(爱神)
- 等下 - 什么事
- Hold up. - What?
你该走了
You need to leave.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
天呐 这样我好尴尬啊
Oh,my God,this is so embarrassing.
你平常也是这样的吗
Is this what you do?
对女人来说 这算哪门子戏法啊
Some kind of sick trick you do to women?
45号 埃文东街
"45 East Evan Street."
别担心 我会给你打电话的
Don't worry about it. I'll call you.
你没我号码
You don't have my number.
我有魔力 我会找到的 祝你晚上愉快
I'm magic. I'll find it. Have a good night.
你真变态
You are such an asshole.
(死神)
(隐士)
(女祭司)
嗨
Hey!
亨利
Henley.
丹尼 你好啊
Danny? Hey.
你拿到卡片了吗
You got a card,huh?
恩 不错 挺好的 恭喜你
No,no,no,it's good for you. Congratulations.
好了 我的打算是这样的
All right,so here's what I'm gonna do,
我先进去打探一下
I'm gonna go inside. I'm gonna scope the place out.
你在外面等着 我马上回来
You wait out here. I will come back
然后接你 行吗 别进来
and get you,okay? Do not come in.
嗨 丹尼我不再是你的助理了
Hey,Danny! I'm not your assistant anymore.
发型不错
Nice hair.
好吧 那你想怎么样
So,actually,what have you been up to?
丹尼 你应该清楚我想怎么样
I think you know exactly what I've been up to,Danny.
我看到了你在我网站所有的匿名留言了
I saw all your anonymous posting on my website.
原来你还有个网站 不错啊
You have a website. That's good.
挺好的 还可以帮你宣传一下
Good for you. Get the word out.
很 好
Okay.
很显然我们不是被单独选中的
So apparently none of us was the only one chosen.
我成了第一个失去自我的人
Let me be the first one to kick my ego to the curb.
行了 打扰一下
Yeah. Excuse me.
- 门是锁着的 - 是吗 我再看下
- Door's locked. - Is it? I'll check.
你 先别说
You. Now,hold it,don't tell me.
海伦 不对
Helen? No,no.
亨利
Henley.
你咖啡杯子上写的有
It's on your coffee cup.
多谢你提醒
Thanks for keeping me honest.
顺便说下 刚那不是什么读心术
That wasn't mentalism,by the way.
只是观察而已
It was just an observation.
再观察一下 你很漂亮
Second observation,you are beautiful.
谢谢你
Thank you.
很好 非常好 精心打造的
That's good. That's very nice. Very well-polished. Nice bit.
我是简 丹尼尔·阿特拉斯 很高兴见到你
J. Daniel Atlas. Nice to meet you.
好吧 我知道你是谁 不过我对你所做的
Very nice. I know who you are and I just want to say that
有点不满意
I'm not interested in you doing
包括你的读心术
your mentalism thing on us.
尤其是在我们都不知真假是非
Especially when we don't know who brought
还有到底是谁引我们过来的情况下
us here or even if it's real.
等下 我感觉到 我感觉到你是个控制狂
Hold on,I'm sensing... I'm sensing you are a control freak.
不好意思 我们之前见过
I'm sorry,have we met before?
这不用读心术也看得出来
It doesn't take a mentalist to figure that out.
你就是个控制狂
You are a control freak.
很好 我就当是在表扬我了
Well,I take that as a compliment.
就他才会把这个当成是赞赏
Only he would take it as a compliment.
很好 不错 又换了种赞赏我的方式
Okay,great. Good. Another compliment.
好吧 这就是你们两个分手的原因
Okay. So that's why you're no longer a couple.
情侣 我们不是的
A couple? No,no.
我们怎么可能是情侣
We were never a couple.
他经常把我锯成两半儿
He used to saw me in half.
她这个助理还挺不错的
She was a very good assistant.
但是丹尼嫌我太肥了
But I was too fat for Danny.
谁说的 我只说过一次 那是因为你连道具的后门都过不去
No. I said that one time because of the trap door.
- 这尺寸很正常 - 这么一点点大小
- There were specs. - You built it this size.
谁能爬过去
No one could fit through there. No one.
丽贝卡就可以
Rebecca fit through.
丽贝卡都钻了几年了
Rebecca fit for years.
你知道钻进那么小的戏服
Do you know how hard it is to stay
就已经很难了吗
in those tiny little costumes?
不知道 我才是主演
No. I'm the main attraction.
所以 他从未让你觉得自己很特别
Okay. So he never made you feel special.
相信我 你应该感到天生与众不同
And,trust me,you deserve to be made to feel special.
这话说的像讲故事一样
That's a really nice story.
祝你们互相捧的愉快
Hope you guys enjoy each other's company.
不会吧
No way.
简 丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
J. Daniel Atlas?
兄弟 我看过你所有的魔术
Dude,I've seen everything that you have ever done.
你就像…
You're like...
我真的很崇拜你
I idolize you. Seriously.
作为一个你的粉丝 真心向你问候
From a true fan. It's so nice to meet you.
顺便说下 我叫杰克
I'm Jack,by the way.
问一下 你有这个吗
Question. Did you get one of these?
有 是死神
Yeah. Death.
我的是女祭司
The High Priestess.
恋人
I'm the Lover.
三分钟热度的恋人
Three minutes.
隐士
Hermit.
那我们现在在这里是… 是在等人吗
So,what are we... Are we waiting for someone?
- 我们为什么不直接 - 门是锁着的
- Why are we just... - The door's locked.
没有东西可以锁住我
Oh,no,nothing's ever locked.
这里是干什么的
What is this place?
哇 我以为我的公寓够脏了
Wow. Thought my apartment was nasty.
天呐 这里真冷
Man,it's freezing in here.
那是什么
What's that?
我不知道
I don't know.
上面说什么
What's it say?
"现在你不能"
"Now you don't."
"玫瑰的别名是…"
"A rose by any other name..."
各位 看看发生什么了
Guys,what's happening?
瞧瞧
Look at that.
是瓦斯
It's gas!
放松 只是干冰而已
Relax. Just dry ice.
好酷
Cool.
等下 你觉得这到底是怎么回事
Wait. What do you think this is all about?
等等…
Hang on. Hang on.
好吧 我什么都没感觉到
I got nothin'.
谢谢你 你刚说的东西真"有意义"
Okay. Thank you. Thank you for the delay.
我只是想创造一个富有智慧的环境
I'm just trying to create the space for wisdom.
好吧 要是佛像没有了灵气
Okay,so you're like Buddha,
那你和他还挺像的
if he wasn't so enlightened.
要是耶稣不自大也没有那么多奇蹟
And you're like Jesus,
那你就长得像耶稣
if he was arrogant and all of his miracles were fake.
行了 一堆基友 你们找个房间行吗
Okay,lovebirds,get a room.
丹尼 说实话 这是不是你弄的
Danny,be honest. Did you do this?
当然不 等下 是你吗
No. Wait,did you?
我也希望是我
I Wish.
为什么没有人问我
Why didn't anyone ask me if I did it?
恩 很好
Oh,great.
这房子没电
Electricity is out.
走 我们过去看看
Well,let's check.
是蓝图
Blueprints.
太不可思议了
They're incredible.
你们觉得是谁做了这些东西
Who do you think did this?
我不知道 不过我很想见见他们
I don't know,but I really want to meet them.
这是演出
It's a show.
《惊天魔盗团》
(拉斯维加斯 一年后)
梅里特·麦金尼
Merritt McKinney,
丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Daniel Atlas,
亨利·里夫斯
Henley Reeves,
杰克·怀尔德
Jack Wilder.
亚瑟·特雷斯特 以及 MGM为您隆重呈现
Arthur Tressler and the MGM Grand proudly presents
四骑士团
The Four Horsemen.
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚我们会尝试一些
Tonight we would like to try something
让更不一样 更高端的魔术
that will,well,set us a bit apart.
也是我们最后的四个表演
For our final trick,
我们会带来一场在拉斯维加斯舞台上
we're gonna do something never before
从未出现过的表演
seen on a Las Vegas stage.
没有任何有名的表演能和我们的相提并论
Or any stage for that matter.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
今晚
tonight
我们将会打劫一家银行
we are going to rob a bank.
犯罪真让人兴奋
That's a lot of excitement for a crime.
我好激动 在座的各位 你们呢
I'm getting excited. What about you,people?
1 2 3
One,two,three!
对不起 先生 表演过程中
Sorry,sir. There's absolutely no recording allowed
不允许录影
during the performance.
是是 行 没问题
Oh,yeah,yeah,sure,of course.
我马上收起来
Let me just put this away.
不好意思 我需要把它带走
Actually,I need to take that.
表演结束了 你可以来领取
After the show,I can come and give it back to you.
好吧
Okay.
好了 好了
Okay,okay.
现在请安静一下
Now,please,please,settle down.
在座的各位有谁的银行想被我们打劫
Now who here has a bank they would like us to rob?
人不可貌相 开银行的人这么多
That's a lot of people with a vendetta.
那么 我们随机从中抽取一位
So we'll choose one at random then.
我的同事会确定是随机抽取的 没问题吧
My associates will make sure it's random. Right?
- "猫王"帮我挑一个 - 非常感谢
- Elvis,help me out,bud. - Thank you very much.
杰克手里的框子里是写着区号的乒乓球
In Jack's bowl are ping pong balls with section numbers.
杰克能递给我一个区域号码吗
Jack,could you hand me a section number?
谢谢 是 B区
Thank you. We are looking at Section B.
B区在哪呢
Where is Section B?
哦 在那 可能就是你们其中的一个人 准备好了
Okay. There. It's gonna be one of you guys. Get ready.
我不知道为什么每个人都这么开心
I don't know why everybody's happy.
就他们B区有机会
It's only them.
梅里特 能帮我抽一下 看是哪排
Merritt,can I get a row,please?
谢谢你 梅里特
Thank you,Merritt.
我们看到的是第五排
We are looking at row number 5.
在哪里
Where is that?
然后亨利 再帮我选一个座位号码
And Henley,could I please have a random seat number?
噢 是幸运数字13
Oh. Lucky number 13.
B-5-13 你在哪里
B-5-13. Where are you?
先生 请起立 你在那呢 你好
Sir,please,stand up. There you are. Hi.
你能再帮我确定一下座位号码吗
Could you just confirm for me that this
看下座位是不是B-5-13
is,in fact,your seat? B-5-13.
千真万确
Yes.
很好 现在请你告诉我们
Okay. Wonderful. Now,could you please tell us
你和你银行的名字
your name and the name of your bank?
恩 我的名字是艾蒂安 福希尔
Well,my name is Etienne Forcier.
我的银行叫巴黎信用合作社
And my bank,it's Credit Republicain de Paris.
法国 好的
French. Okay.
我们还希望是近一点的
We were hoping for something a little more local,
那种本地夫妻经营的小银行 没什么保安的那种
a kind of mom-and-pop credit union with no security.
不过没关系 承诺就是承诺
But that's fine. A promise is a promise.
你能上来舞台这里吗
Could you please come up to the stage
然后我们就开始抢劫你的银行
and we'll rob your bank.
与此同时
And while he does that...
还有一位今晚也值得一提
There is someone here tonight
没了他 我们四个
without whom we would just be
可能还在马戏团当小魔术师
four magicians working the circuit,
然后还要摸爬滚打
trying to get...
才能有今天的位置
Well,actually,trying to get here.
就算你不是他众多
You probably know this man,
公司的一员
if not from one of the many,many
你也可能认识他
companies he puts his name on.
他就是我们的朋友 我们的赞助商
He is our friend. He is our benefactor.
亚瑟·特雷斯特先生
Mr. Arthur Tressler.
请起立 阿特 麻烦您站起来
Please,stand up,Art. Please,stand up.
他是这里在座的唯一一个
The only man here with
拥有女皇号码的人
the Queen's cell phone number.
如果可以 请继续站会儿 阿特
Actually,please,stay standing,Art.
我想说 当我们找到特雷斯勒的时候
I want to say that when we came to Mr. Tressler,
我们保证过 作为一个团体
we promised that,as a unit,we could become
我们会成为最伟大的魔术师
the biggest name in magic.
所以我们想说"谢谢"
So we wanted to say,"Thank you."
然后顺便再说一句 阿特 你看到了前排的名单了吗
And by the way,Art,you notice on the sign out front,
我们已经确保你的名字在第一位了
we made sure we put your name on top.
亲爱的小女孩 如果你想证明自己有你
If you turn out to be as good
自己所想的那么好
as you think you are,dear girl,
那么这个也就没有这么重要了
that won't be necessary much longer.
我们还没有进行最后的表演呢
We haven't done our closer yet.
你何不先看一下
Why don't you watch it
然后再做决定
and then you can decide for yourself.
女士们 先生们 这就是亚瑟·特雷斯特
Ladies and gentlemen,Arthur Tressler!
谢谢你 然后 再一次把掌声给
Thank you. And,of course,once again,the Cardinal of Clairvoyance,
主角梅里特·麦金尼
Merritt McKinney.
艾蒂安 杰克带来的是我们魔术界
Etienne,what Jack is bringing to the stage now,
的传送头盔
is what we in the magic world call a teleportation helmet.
你需要带着这个 因为它能
You will need to wear this,as it will allow you
扭曲时空和时间
to literally fold through space and time
带你去你的银行
to your bank in the...
8号
8th?
- 9号 行政区大街 - 是的
- 9th arrondissement. - Yeah.
好的 一旦你到那之后
Now,once you are there,
我们就只能通过这个头盔和你对话了
we will be able to speak with you through this helmet.
如果…
NOW if...
噢 天呐 太帅气了
Oh,my God,that's beautiful.
时髦之中 又添几分吸引力
It has the added attraction of being very stylish.
是时候 法国向美国学学什么叫时髦了
It's about time the French learned from America on that subject.
真是个美丽的头饰 对吧
Is that a beautiful piece of headgear?
- 谢谢 谢谢 - 的确是
- Thank you. Thank you... - it is.
谢谢 十分感谢
Thank you. Thank you very much.
但 在你出发之前
But before you go anywhere,
请抽一张牌
could you please,pick a card,any card.
哦 不是这张
Not that card.
没事 这是个老掉牙的美国笑话 你可以拿刚那张
No,that's an old American joke. You can take that one.
好了 就这个了吗
Okay. This one?
给你B区的朋友看看 但是别被我们看到
Show it to your friends in Section B. But not to us.
好的 很好 把你的名字签上去
Okay,great. Now if you could just sign your name there.
- 好 - 如果能用英语最好
- Yes. - In English,if possible.
- 很好 - 谢谢
- That's good. - Thanks.
放到你口袋里去
Put it in your pocket.
现在 还有一点小细节没有处理
And now for one tiny detail.
现在 艾蒂安 请走进这个复杂的机器
Now,Etienne,let's step into this cockamamie contraption.
我呢 从里面走出来 祝你好运
And I'll step off of it. Bonne chance.
现在拉斯维加斯是晚上11点50
It's 11:50 p.m. here in Vegas.
巴黎呢是早上8点50分
That's 8:50 a.m. in Paris.
你的银行还有不到10分钟就开门了
Your bank opens in less than 10 minutes.
一
One,
two...
三
Three.
什么情况
What the fuck?
- 艾蒂安 - 艾蒂安
- Efienne? - Efienne?
应该不是这样的啊 是吗
It wasn't supposed to happen like that,was it?
艾蒂安
Efienne?
我还挺喜欢那个法国小伙儿的
I liked that little French guy.
他去哪里了
Where did he go?
(巴黎 在同一时刻)
等等 他在那里
Wait,there he is.
别别别 大家别吵
No,no,no,no,please,please,please.
我是丹尼尔·阿特拉斯 你听得到我说话吗
This is Daniel Atlas. Can you hear me?
艾蒂安 你没事吧
Etienne? Are you okay?
没事
Yes.
很好 你在里面看到什么了
Perfect. What do you see in there?
钱…
Money.
真的吗
Is this real?
是的 看起来有三百万欧元
Yes. Looks like three million or so Euros' worth.
很好 现在我们需要你做点事
Okay,now,here's what we're gonna need you to do.
请你把刚那张牌
I want you to take the card that you signed
从你口袋里拿出来
out of your pocket.
然后带着你今晚的
And I want you to take the ticket stub
入场券
from tonight's show
然后把它放在
and I want you to put it right there
钱的正中央
in the middle of the money.
丢吧
Now drop it.
现在 你摸摸看你头盔侧面有个按钮
Now,on the side of your helmet you should feel a button.
先别按
Don't press it just yet.
那个按钮可以启动链接巴黎和拉斯维加斯
That button activates an air duct
的空气管道
that connects Paris to Las Vegas.
很好 你现在可以按了
Okay,good. Now you can press it.
好 艾蒂安 准备好了
All right,now,Etienne,hold on tight.
你可能会感觉到一点点真空感
You might feel a bit of a vacuum.
等等
Wait a second.
谢谢你 艾蒂安 谢谢各位
Thank you,Etienne. Thank you,everyone!
我们是四骑士团
We are The Four Horsemen.
晚安各位
And good night!
晚安
Good night!
在这等下
Hold up here.
我是迪伦 罗兹
Dylan Rhodes.
什么 我听错了吗
What? I don't think I heard you correctly.
你刚是说魔术师吗
Did you say magicians?
是的迪伦 是魔术师
Yeah,Dylan,magicians.
你现在在哪里
Where are you now?
我在亚里亚 我正过去逮捕他们
I'm at Aria. I'm heading up there to grab 'em now.
FBI手放到我可以看到的地方
FBI! Hands where I can see them.
起来 快点
Let's go. Get 'em up. Come on.
走 抓他们起来
Let's go. Get 'em up.
把书放下
Put the book down.
好了 你抓到我了
Okay. You got me.
- 别动 手举高 - 噢 天
- Freeze! Hands in the air! - Oh,my!
你们有没有人可以帮我们提下包
Do one of you guys mind giving us a hand with our bags?
走吧
Let's go.
老大 告诉我这不是真的
Boss,please tell me this is a joke.
我刚刚收到威利·米尔斯指认波利·阿塔纳西奥
I just got Willy Mears to finger Paulie Attanasio.
我一个月最多两次
I'm a month,two tops,
已经忙得炸开了锅了
away from blowing this whole thing open.
你找特克尔森
Get Turkelson.
他就在亚特兰大市
He's in Atlantic City.
或者考恩 你看看他
What about Cowan? Look at him.
屁股都粘在板凳上了
He's just sitting there on his ass.
罗兹 你真喜剧
Hilarious,Rhodes.
我爱你
I love you.
蠢货
Asshole.
我没有时间管这些什么魔术师
I don't have time for this magic crap.
这些人渣刚从巴黎银行偷了三百万欧元
This crap just pulled three million Euro out of a Parisian bank.
- 那全是他们拿的 - 是的
- That's how much they got? - Yeah.
事实上是320万
Actually,3.2.
她是谁
Who is she?
你是谁
Who are you?
阿尔玛 德雷 法国国际刑警
Alma Dray from Interpol.
我会和你一起展开调查
I'll be working the investigation with you.
你是在开玩笑吗
You gotta be kidding me.
大卫 科波菲尔和几个朋友
It's bad enough they got me chasing down
我就己经够呛的了
David Copperfield and Friends.
现在又来一个…国际刑警 没有别的意思 别误会
Now I'm being saddled with,no offense,with Interpol?
我也很高兴和你合作调查 罗兹
I look forward to working with you,too,Agent Rhodes.
对不起 我不觉得我需要你的帮助 懂吗
I'm sorry. I don't think I'm gonna need your help on this. Okay?
- 那个法国人呢 - 我已经跟他谈过了
- Where's the French guy? - I already spoke to him.
哦 是吗 你在我之前跟我的目击证人说话
Oh,you did? You spoke to my witness before me?
你的目击证人 我还以为你不想管这个案子
Your witness? I thought you didn't want the case.
再说了 他基本上没用
Besides,he's useless.
哦 是吗 为什么这么说
Oh,really? Why is that?
因为他相信魔术是真的
Because he believes their magic was real.
噢 他觉得是真的
Oh,he believes the magic was real?
你说的对 那他真可能没有用
You're right,he probably is useless.
如果你没问题 我们一起再去跟他谈谈
Is it okay with Interpol if we talk to him,too?
谢谢
Thank you.
我一生中从未偷过任何一样东西 明白吗
I have never stolen a thing in my life,okay?
我试过把钱还回去 但是他们不要
I tried to give the money back,but they won't take it.
好了好了 这么说吧 你抢了一家银行
Okay,okay,okay,let's just say you robbed a bank.
- 我做的 - 很好 你承认了 就你做的
- I did. - Fine. Fantastic. You did.
但是我还是这方面的新手 你能解释下
But since I'm new to this,can you explain to me how you went
你如何在3秒内从拉斯维加斯去到巴黎的吗
from Las Vegas to Paris in three seconds?
用的是传送头盔
With the teleportation helmet.
好吧 是他疯了还是我疯了
Okay,what the hell is going on here?
他在表演的时候被催眠了
He was hypnotized during the show.
我告诉过你 他没有用了
I told you,he's useless.
好吧 我一会儿问完了其他的
Okay,I'll deal with you when I'm clone
东西再跟你算账
with this other bullshit.
嘿
Hey!
表演期间 一般的观众都被催眠
During the show,half the audience was hypnotized
认为自己在交响乐队
to believe they were in the Philharmonic.
我认为"bullshit"就是触发这个的机关
I guess that "bullshit" was the trigger word.
好了 艾蒂安 下来
Okay. Hey,hey. Ecoutez. Etienne,come on down from there.
你不在交响乐团
You're not in the Philharmonic.
- 法语的"停止"怎么说 - 就是"Stop"
- How do you say "stop" in French? - Stop.
那你叫他停下来
Tell him to stop.
我做不到 你必须等他跳完
No,I can't. You just have to let him finish his movement.
好吧 我需要休息一下
Okay,I need a time-out.
受不了了 全是法国人
Too many French people in one room.
特工罗兹
Agent Rhodes!
我的上级命令我提供一份报告
I'm ordered by my bosses to provide a report.
直到完成任务 我都在这里 不管你乐不乐意
And until we have one,I'm here,like it or not.
因此 我们可以一起办事
So we can work together,
或者你可以跟在我后面问
or you can continue to follow behind
我之前已经问过的话
asking the same exact questions I'm asking.
随便你了
It's up to you.
我还没说完
I'm not finished.
我刚飞了12个小时 过了这么久的一个白天
I just flew 12 hours,after what was already a long day.
我还没能适应时差
And I do not handle jet lag well.
如果你想看看谁的脾气更大
So if you want to see who can be grumpier,
我保证你输得很彻底
I promise you,you will lose.
很好 那这些白痴里面 你想
Fine. So which one of these idiots
先和谁谈
do you want to talk to first?
他
Him?
迪伦 先提醒你一下
Dylan,for the record,
读心术从未准确的验过是真是假
mentalism has never actually been proven to be accurate.
知道了
Okay.
这么说的话 那就不是科学了
That is to say,that it's not a science.
听起来更像娱乐
It's more for entertainment.
好了
All right.
只要不相信他讲的东西 就可以了
Just don't believe everything the guy says. That's all.
请转达我对你外面
Please convey my deepest apologies
那位同事的深深的歉意
to your colleague out there.
很抱歉给你带来了一个完全不一样的周二
I'm really sorry about this whole Tranny Tuesday thing.
我实在是太不对了
I was out of line.
不一样的周二
Tranny Tuesday?
好吧 这是他跟他老婆的安排
Well,it's an arrangement he and his wife have.
如果你相信富勒说的
Or might not have,if you believe
所有的东西都是对的 也有可能并没有安排好
everything Agent Fuller is saying to be correct.
但FBI是不是有一个让你们自豪
But isn't there a proud tradition in the FBI
的传统就是男人穿裙子
of men wearing dresses?
不要不好意思 富勒 没关系的
No shame,Agent Fuller. No shame.
我觉得好过瘾啊
I'm just having fun.
这是你刚抽的牌吗 不 不是的
Was this your card? No.
看到了吗 我知道你的不是红桃
See,I knew you weren't a queen of hearts lady,
但是我相信
and I respect that.
如果我没有被绑在这里 我会变得更好
The trick usually works better when I'm not strapped in here,
但是我了解 走过场嘛
but I understand protocol.
好了 行了
Okay,okay.
那么 如果跟你半点关系没有
So,if you had nothing to do with it,
那么那张牌是怎么进去的
then how did the playing card get into the vault?
噢 这样啊
Oh,yes. That would be...
现在的孩子们都管这个叫
What do the kids call it these days?
哦 对 叫魔法
Oh,yes,that's right. Magic.
回答我的问题 别自作聪明
Just answer the question,okay,smartass.
好的 对不起 对不起
All right. Sorry,sorry,sorry.
你可以拿走 但别给他看
You can keep that. Don't share it with him.
据说你会读心术
It says here you are a mentalist.
读心术到底是什么
What exactly is mentalism?
算是把戏吧 又有一些科学
Tricks,mostly. Some science.
有针对性的猜测 可以算是最准确的描述了
Targeted guessing might be a most apt description.
然后伴着一些直觉和偶然
Along with some intuition and the occasional...
还有出现在我脑海里的声音
Voices in my head.
这里说你曾一度很有名
Says here you were fairly famous at one point.
说你甚至可以通过电话催眠别人
You can even hypnotize people over the phone.
环美旅行几年
Some big tours around the U.S. for a few years,
- 参加过两次电视节目 - 《荣耀时光》
- two TV specials. - Glory days.
然后你的弟弟/管理员
Then your brother/manager
带着你来之不易的钱玩失踪
disappeared with all your hard-earned money.
你调查过我 是吧
Did your research,did you?
国税局审计后 又补缴税款
IRS audit. Back taxes.
经过很久的努力
You've had a long hard slog back
你才成为公众的焦点 对吧
into the limelight,haven't you,Mr. McKinney?
是啊 那当然
Yes,indeed,
我对那次旅行还挺感激的
it has. And I do appreciate that trip down Memory Lane.
我只知道 当那个法国男人带上
As far as I understand it,when the man from Paris
魔法头盔之后
put on the magical helmet...
听我说
Listen to me.
如果你没有抢银行 那你应该知道谁干的
If you didn't rob that bank,then you knew about it.
那你也就是共犯
Which makes you an accomplice.
如果你今天想从这里出去 我建议你开始…
So if you wanna walk out of here today,I'd suggest you start...
你听我说 除非你想
Now you listen to me,unless you think
如果内华达州有地区检察官
there's a D.A. in the state of Nevada
那他应该乐意跟陪审团解释这件事
who'd be willing to make sense of this to a jury,
那么我们就还会有一次表演机会
then we have a show to perform.
至于你 罗兹特工
And you,Agent Rhodes,
你也有机会重新实施你的计划了
have a drawing board to get back to.
这是你们第一次约会吧
Is this your first date?
什么
What?
没事 我是说 很显然
No,I mean,obviously,
你们两个人可能互相一点都不认识
you guys don't know each other well,if at all.
这房间里氛围已经是剑拔弩张了
But,like,there is a palpable tension in this room.
在你被卷入这事之前
And before you get involved,
你要考虑清楚 她可是有一堆秘密的哦
you should consider the fact that she has a lot of big secrets.
我知道 她第一个秘密是
And I know the first one is that
这是你第一次不做文职 对吧
this is your first time off the desk. Isn't it?
你应该告诉他的
You should have said something to him.
这居然还是我告诉你的 不会感觉怪怪的吗
This is a weird way for you to find out.
你是想求着被抓走 是吗
You are literally begging to be arrested. You know that?
如果你真的要抓 那我就认了 不过你不会抓的
If it means you would actually do it,then,yeah. But you won't.
因为如果你抓了 那就说明你
Because if you did,it means that you,
和FBI还有你国际刑警的朋友
and the FBI,and your friends at Interpol,
在直觉层面上相信了魔法
actually believe,at an institutional level,in magic.
各大媒体就又有得忙了
The press would have a field day.
那么我们就会比我们现在更出名
And we'd be even more famous than we already are.
然后你们看起来就跟傻瓜一样
And you guys would look like idiots
甚至比现在看起来还要傻
even more then you already are.
好吧 不包括你 但他肯定傻 对吧
Well,no,not you. But him. Right?
你这种在我们魔术界叫
You have,what we in the business,like to call,
"老实巴交"
"nothing up your sleeve."
你自己也知道这点的
And you know it.
别把他牵扯进来然后又抛弃他
Don't draw him in and then dump him
因为抛弃对他来说是个很恐怖的"词汇"
because abandonment is a big "area" for him.
妈咪
Mommy?
爹地
Daddy.
你有恋父情结
You have big daddy issues.
- 好了 够了 - 我告诉你
- Okay,that's enough. - I'll tell you what.
你这种情况平均治疗费用
Your average therapist is gonna charge you
一般是200-300美元
$200-$300 for this sesh.
我呢 收你10块吧
Me? I'll take a tenner.
好吧 迟些再看吧 如果你不觉得没面子
Okay,later,if you're feeling magnanimous,
我还是只收你10块
I'll still take a tenner.
你想知道之前还有谁坐在你现在这个位置吗
You wanna know who sat in that chair before you?
黑帮老大 杀人犯还有小偷
Mob bosses,murderers,and thieves.
你知道是谁抓他们来这儿的吗
And you know who put them there?
抓他们来的人 是现在坐在我这个位置的人
The guy who's sitting in this chair.
所以我警告你 我可以咬着你一辈子不放
So I warn you,I can maintain my resolve much longer
而你的虚假嚣张气焰最多维持一时
than you can maintain that phony arrogance.
告诉你 只要你这张自鸣得意的脸庞
And the instant that you even show
露出半点蛛丝马迹
the slightest crack in that smug facade,
我就会瞬间出现在你身边 逮捕你
I'll be there.
我会在时刻监视着你 就像…
I will be all over you like...
就像狗皮膏药
Like white on rice?
不好意思 说话太直接了
Sorry. That's unfair.
警告你
Let me warn you.
我想你 不要放弃这个案子
I want you to follow.
因为 即便你觉得自己好像了如指掌了
Because no matter what you think you might know,
我们其实都早已料到
we will always be one step,three steps,
你的下一步是什么
seven steps ahead of you.
当你感觉好像要追上我们的思路的时候
And just when you think you're catching up,
那正将是我们在你后面伏击你的时候
that's when we'll be right behind you.
你出现在任何地方
And at no time will you be anywhere other than
都是我精心设计好的
exactly where I want you to be.
所以 跟的再近一点 试着形影不离吧
So come close. Get all over me
因为 你越觉得自己很近
because the closer you think you are,
你能看到的东西就越少
the less you'll actually see.
我会抓住你
I'm gonna nail you...
小姐 苏打水不好喝吗
Something wrong with that soda,Miss?
哦 呵呵
Oh! Shit!
魔法第一法则
First rule of magic.
我永远是这房间里最聪明的一个
Always be the smartest guy in the room.
老大 这就放他们走了
Boss,what are we doing? We're letting them go?
他们全部都只说 他们会再偷一次
They all but admitted they're gonna do it again.
但半小时前 你还觉得他们都一无是处
About a half an hour ago,you didn't give a damn about them.
- 怎么突然变了 - 因为我见过他们了
- What changed? - I met them.
嘿 你们俩
Hey. Guys.
我刚又彻查了一遍观众
Hey,I ran a check on the audience.
大部分都是特雷斯勒给钱
Most of it was just filler.
要他们去充场子的
People that Tressler dragged in to pack the room.
但是你们知道是谁
But guess who was sitting there in the back,
一直坐在后面录下了整个过程吗
filming the whole damn thing?
不知道
I don't know.
是赛迪斯·布莱德利
Thaddeus Bradley.
布莱德利就是那个电视里经常表演节目的人 你不知道？
Thaddeus Bradley,the guy from TV with the DVDs and shows?
不知道
No.
好吧 他是经常解密魔术的一个人
Okay,well,he debunks magicians.
他喜欢曝光他们 他会演示他们是怎么变的
He exposes them. He shows you how to do their tricks.
立刻打电话给他
Get him on the phone.
已经联系了 你11点45跟他见面
I did. You're having lunch with him in 45.
很好
Good.
布莱德利以前也曾是魔术师
Mr. Bradley started as a magician.
- 他以前挺厉害的 - 是吗
- He was actually quite good. - Really?
- 最厉害的其中一个 - 不用你说
- One of the best. - You don't say.
"智者往往能够看透表面"
"The greatest genius is in seeing through the illusion."
他还真热爱他的事业
That's a man who loves his work.
你确定不用喝杯酒吗
You sure I can't interest you in a glass of wine?
不不不 谢谢你 我们在工作
No,no,no. No,thank you,sir. We're working.
给我来杯吧
I will take one.
太不可思议了 太神奇了
That's incredible. That's amazing.
红燃料而已 雕虫小技
Red dye,palmed.
这太难以置信了 跟上帝耍戏法儿一样
Is that how Jesus did it? That's incredible.
不好意思 我能打扰一会儿吗
I'm sorry. Can I just take a minute here?
你也曾是伟大的魔术师 为什么又不做这行了
You were one of the great magicians. Why did you stop?
你知道这5年来 有多少人想看到
Do you know how many people went to see magic performed live
魔术解密直播吗
in the last half decade?
大约有160万
About 1.6 million.
你知道这些年我卖了多少DVD吗
You know how many DVDs I sold in the same period?
5百万
Five million.
那这么说 是因为钱了
Right,so it's about the money.
这么说吧 有钱赚也是因为
Well,the money is only there
渴望答案要比渴望被耍 强烈很多
because the need to know is greater than the desire to be fooled.
就像你 我很讨厌
Like you,I detest those
以欺骗民众为生的人
who prey upon the gullibility of the masses.
无意冒犯 难道没有什么代价吗
With all due respect,isn't there a cost,though,to this game?
代价
Cost?
我只知道求生计
I don't know. Careers.
养家糊口
Lives.
我猜你说的应该是 莱昂内尔·史瑞克吧
I assume you're referring to Lionel Shrike.
对不起 他是
I'm sorry,who?
莱昂内尔·史瑞克
Lionel Shrike.
一个二流魔术师30年前在哈德逊河被淹死了
A middling magician who drowned in the Hudson River 30 years ago.
在布莱德利先生的节目上
On Mr. Bradley's first special,
他揭秘了史瑞克所有的把戏
he revealed all of Shrike's tricks.
第二年 史瑞克决定东山再起
The next year,Shrike tried to stage a comeback.
他被铐在一个保险柜里面
He was shackled inside a safe,
然后丢进河里
and dropped into the river.
不过就再也没有浮起来了
But he never resurfaced.
你是说 他死了
You mean he died?
我没有杀他
I didn't kill him.
他过于急功近利
He killed himself
根本没准备好就表演 最后踉成惨剧
trying to do something he wasn't prepared to handle.
你觉得魔术是游戏吗
You do realize this is a game?
相信我 肯定不是游戏
Believe me,it's not a game.
其实就是游戏
It is a game.
玩的就是你
You're the game. You're being played.
别害躁 我意思就是说你阿谀奉承
And your pathetic attempts at fawning to gain my trust...
不就是为了获得我的信任吗
I mean,come on.
你真了解我
You got me.
如果你真想知道 巴黎的银行怎么会
If you really want to know
在拉斯维加斯的一个舞台上被盗了
how a bank in Paris was robbed from a stage in Las Vegas,
敬请关注我下期节目
my special comes out next month.
那我就告你妨碍公务
Or I could just bring you in
抓你去告诉我
on obstruction charges and force you to tell me.
当然 除非你努力解释给我说
Unless,of course,what you're trying to say to me is that
你其实压根儿不知道他们怎么变的
you actually don't know how they did it.
都是障眼法和舞台效果
Showmanship and theatrics.
当一个魔术师舞动双手 说
When a magician waves his hand and says,
"接下来就是见证奇蹟的时刻"
"This is where the magic is happening."
这个时候 其实真正变化是发生在其他地方的
The real trick is happening somewhere else.
误导法 魔术的基本概念
Misdirection. A basic concept of magic.
我对魔术的概念不感兴趣
Not interested in the concepts of magic.
我只想知道他们怎么抢银行的
I wanna know how they robbed a bank.
如果你真觉得 他们当时抢了银行 那你真是个白痴
You're an idiot if you think they robbed a bank.
恕我多言
But don't take my word for it.
现在来说下 瞬间转移到巴黎
How about a trip to Paris?
赫米亚 传送头盔 你不会当真吧
Hermia,the teleportation helmet,please,darling?
你开玩笑的吧
You're joking,right?
你想知道他们是怎么办到的吗
You wanna know how they did it or not?
我现在把这个给你带上
I'm just gonna put this on your head.
上去吧
Step right up.
就这样
There you go.
现在我们慢慢把这个拉下来
Now we just pull this down all safe and snug.
随意点 就这样
Make yourself comfortable. There we go.
然后 当你准备好去巴黎了
And when you're ready to go to Paris,
就故弄玄虚一下 说个魔法词汇
just say the magic word.
给我吹
Blow me?
- 这也足够 - 一路顺风
- That'll suffice. - Bon voyage.
我觉得还是走楼梯舒服点
I personally prefer to take the stairs to Paris.
欢迎来到灯光之城巴黎
Welcome to the City of Light,Agent Rhodes.
呵 呵 呵 这头盔没用吗
Hardy har har. What was with the helmet?
用来调戏你的
My fun.
什么
What?
没什么
Nothing.
这么说 他们有个地下室
So they got a vault set.
是的
Yes.
然后和那法国家伙的银行
And it's the exact replica
一模一样
of the little French guy's bank.
那他就是托儿
So he's a plant.
他不是托儿 他是被骗了
He was a dupe,not a plant.
他们选他是因为他们知道他坐哪里
They chose him. They knew which seat he was in.
不不不 是观众选的座位
No,no,no,the audience picked the seat.
当然不是观众选的座位
Unless,of course,the audience didn't pick the seat.
而是"让"大家觉得的确是观众自己选的
They let them think they picked the seat.
那么我们来随机抽取一个
We'll choose one at random then.
其实他们把手中的球换成了
Actually,they were just palming the ball
他们想要的座位号码
with the seat number they wanted.
我们抽到了5号
We are looking at row number 5.
亨利 再帮我挑一个座位号
Henley,could I please have a seat number?
幸运数字13
Lucky number 13.
您能再确认下座位是对的吗
Could you just confirm that this is,in fact,your seat?
其实他早就被选好了
He was selected.
他们早就催眠他 让他去拉斯维加斯
They programmed his mind to make him go to Las Vegas.
拉斯维加斯万岁
Viva Las Vegas.
然后通过不同方式来强调维加斯 直到他真的去了维加斯
And then they kept reinforcing it,until he did.
紧接着 跟踪他
They trailed him.
研究他
They studied him.
以确保万无一失
Nothing was left to chance.
我测到他头部尺寸了
I got his measurements.
成了他们的目标 自己却浑然不知
He had no idea he was their target.
然后他们假装把他从维加斯送走
And they simply activated him in Vegas.
当我打响指…
When I snap my fingers...
好的 再次热烈掌声给梅里特·麦金尼
And once again,Merritt McKinney.
但怎么知道他们银行是哪家
But how did they know what bank was his?
- 你还不懂啊 - 谁能懂
- You're kidding. - Really?
你能别故作高深吗
Can you be any more of a condescending ass?
好吧
Yes.
就像这样
Like this.
通过一种非常神秘 不常见的手段
There's a very rare,very mysterious way
魔术师们就知道哪家银行属于他
in which a magician divines an audience member's bank.
准备好了吗
You ready?
好了
Yes.
信用卡
Credit card.
他们就是这样把带有签名的牌
And that's how they got the signature for the card
留在了巴黎银行的地下室
they left in the vault in Paris.
非常正确
Very good.
你已经领先一步了 罗兹
You're being one-upped,Agent Rhodes.
但他们必须把签名的扑克放到那个地下室
Okay,but they had to get the signature card in the vault.
你说他们没有偷钱
You said they didn't steal the money.
不啊 我没说他们没有偷钱
No,I didn't say they didn't steal the money.
我只说了他们没有打劫银行
I said they didn't rob the bank.
我猜测是这样的
My guess is that they targeted
他们看中了开往那家银行的装甲卡车
a shipment of freshly minted money
上面新鲜出炉的钱
headed to the Frenchman's bank on-board an armored truck.
当然进去很难
Which,of course,is just as hard to break into.
除非…你已经在里面了
Unless you're already inside.
不管银行让你觉得他们是有多安全
And despite what the banks would have you believe,
但是这些开车的人绝对不可靠
the men who drive these trucks are not exactly mental giants.
而对我们的四骑士团来说
For our Horsemen,
这就太简单了
it was almost too easy.
那他们是怎么让那些地下室的
So,how did they make the fake
假钞凭空消失的 你解释下
money disappear from the vault? What is that?
魔术火纸
Flash paper.
魔术师一般都用这个
Magicians use it all the time.
燃烧之后没有烟 没有残渣
Creates no smoke,leaves no residue.
两天前 这些家伙都还名不见经传
Two days ago,no one heard of these guys,
但今晚的表演门票35秒就已售罄
but tonight's show sold out in 35 seconds.
看似这些人对如何运作生意 已经初窥门径
I think these guys have cracked the secret to show business.
你给了观众三百万
Give your audience $3 million.
让他们好好演 对吧
Puts 'em in a good mood,doesn't it?
压轴的才是最好的
Best finale ever.
他们的表演将会永垂不朽
They're gonna be the first magicians in history to get laid.
记住了要是飞机氧气面罩掉下来了
Remember,if the oxygen mask comes down,
- 记得先给你的律师带上 - 哦 必须的
- put it on the lawyer first. Remember. - Oh,yes.
我会的 一定给律师先带
I always do. It's lawyer first,
- 然后才给自己带 接着给孩子带 - 然后你自己
- then myself and then the children. - Then yourself.
是的 然后才轮到小孩
Yes. Then the children.
让我说说 我们大家都在想什么
Allow me to make plain what we've both been thinking.
嗯 你说
And what's that?
很显然 你对丹尼尔有好感
Well,obviously,you have feelings of affection for Daniel.
但是却一直没有得到回应
Unrequited and misguided,
都怪他情商过低
owing to his lack of emotional availability.
因此 你一直深深地…
Consequently,you're very tightly...
怎么说好呢
How should I put it?
憋着
Corked.
哦 我是这样的
Oh,lam?
现在呢 意识到自己身理上得不到满足
Now,recognizing that you have physical needs not being met,
然后就抠破脑袋 帮你妹妹解决这方面的问题
and strictly in the vein of helping a sister out,
你可以考虑下我 帮你私下"排忧解难"
I invite you to think of me as your own personal corkscrew.
哇 谢谢了
Wow. Thanks.
如此廉价的机会 我得深思熟虑下
Let me mull over that offer of cheap and meaningless sex.
可能是很廉价无意义 但是又不花时间
Cheap and meaningless,maybe,but not time-consuming.
飞机将会提前几分钟抵达目的地
We should be getting there a few minutes early.
放松自己
So,sit back,relax.
很快将会抵达纽奥良
We should be in the Big Easy soon.
感谢您乘坐此次航班
Appreciate you flying with us today.
那你说 特雷斯勒有什么好处 除了钱之外
So,what's in it for Tressler,besides the money?
自我层面
Ego.
好 选张牌
Okay,pick your card.
看一下 然后放回牌堆 别告诉我是什么
Look at it,put it in the deck,and tell me.
噢 别让我知道了
No,don't tell me.
- 好了 - 行了
- Okay. - Okay.
萨帝厄斯 那晚在那里
Thaddeus was there that night.
他应该清楚 问问他怎么样
He knows exactly how they pulled it off. What about him?
你是说
What are you saying?
他们可能是一伙儿的
You think they could be working together.
我也不知道 我所知道的就是
I don't know. All I know is that these guys
这些家伙一年前是无名鼠辈
were a bunch of street magicians
没钱没资源
a year ago with no resources.
你说 如果没有外界的帮助的话
So,how do they go from doing that to this
他们怎么开始着手干这些的
without some kind of outside help?
这是你刚的牌
Is this your card?
没有 我刚那张牌 在那哥们大腿上
No,my card is sitting over there in that guy's lap.
变得好
Nice shuffle.
你不知道 这真的很难
You know,this is hard.
这本书上说
According to this book,
一些很简单的动作
some of those guys
有一些人每天要练习8小时 一练就是几年
practice one simple move eight hours a day for years.
是吗 那这些人真应该找份事做
Really? Some of those guys seriously need to get a life.
你是不是对魔术师 有抵触情绪
Is it magicians,in general,you have a problem with?
还是说那几个人
Or specifically those guys?
魔术师并没什么
I could care less about magicians in general.
我讨厌的是为牟利 而利用别人的混蛋
What I hate is people who exploit other people.
怎么利用
Exploit them how?
再抽一张
Try again.
利用他人弱点
By taking advantage of their weaknesses.
以及他人的天真
Their need to believe in something that's unexplainable
来维持生计
in order to make their lives more bearable.
我觉得这是优势
I see it as a strength.
天真一点 我的一生会更开心
My life is happier when I believe that.
这是你的牌了吧
Is this your card?
是的
Yeah.
真的吗
Yeah?
- 是的 - 太酷了
- Yeah. - Cool.
刚你笑了 不是假装的吧
That smile on your face. Is it real?
可能吧
Maybe.
那我问你 大侦探先生
So let me ask you,Mr. Detective Man.
你有没有觉得被利用了
Do you feel exploited?
还是说 你觉得有一点点好玩
Or did you have maybe a tiny,tiny bit of fun?
有一个男的去看病
Guy goes to the doctor.
医生说: "先生"
Doctor says,"Sir,you're gonna
"你不能再自慰了"
"have to stop masturbating."
他问到"为什么"
He Says,"Why?"
医生说"这样我可以早点下班"
He says,"So I can finish the examination."
噢 丹尼 能跟你简单的谈一下
Oh,Danny,can I talk to you about
- 表演里我的角色吗 - 是 是 是 没问题
- my role in the show real quick? - Yeah,yeah,yeah. Sure.
嘿 伙计们
Hey,guys.
我们有表演要准备了
We got a show to prepare for.
现在吗
Do we now?
走开 别对我用那招
No,no,no,don't do that.
你那招对我没用的 别试了
You're not doing that thing to me. No.
什么东西 看你以眼不行啊
What thing? I'm just looking at you.
你就是想催眠我 我观察你一整年了
No,you're not. I've been watching you for a year.
我知道你的小把戏
I know all of your little tricks.
对你来说 我这些全是小把戏
That what they are to you? Tricks?
对啊 都说是骗人的
Yes,it's gimmicks. it's Barnum statements.
不就是看眼神 肢体语言 我也会
It's reading the eyes. Body language. I get it.
如果真这么容易 你怎么不对亨利试下
If it's such an easy thing,why don't you do Henley?
对啊 丹尼 你怎么不来试试我
Yeah,Danny. Why don't you do me?
不用了 你太容易了 我还是试下贾斯敏
No,you're too easy. I'll do Jasmine.
不
No.
来试试我
Do me.
噢 对啊 你试试阿特看
Oh,yeah. Yeah. Do Art.
行
Okay.
防着他点
Even better.
- 阿特 - 来吧
- Art. - Yeah.
不过我警告你 如果我不想被读心
But I warn you,I can be difficult to read,
那就没那么容易
when I want to be.
仔细看着我 好吗
Just stay with me,okay?
阿特 说你小时候很坚强
So,Art,you were a tough kid.
你懂的 那种流氓恶棍都欺负的对象
You know,kind of a real rapscallion.
你有一只狗 也很坚强
You had a dog. A real tough dog.
比较粗暴的品种 就像…
A brutish breed. Like a real...
斗牛犬
I want to say,Ben the bulldog.
我实际上是个比较谨慎的小孩
Actually,I was a prissy little tot.
我养了只白色 毛比较蓬松的猫 名字叫"斯纳佛"
I had a fluffy white cat called Snuffles.
对不起
Sorry.
要不让我试试
Wait,let me try one.
- 我可以猜的比他准很多 - 让他试试
- I can do way better than that. - Let him do it.
别这样啊 再给我次机会 就一次
Come on,give me one more time. One more time.
他能猜得更准点
He can do way better than that.
这次我们来猜猜家庭方面的
Let's do family.
你妈妈那边你有个舅舅
You had an uncle on your mother's side.
他的名字很男人
He had a real,kind of... A real masculine name.
一种有点像社会精英
A real,kind of,salt-of-the-earth...
你知道 有点难的
You know,a real stick-it-to-you...
比如 保罗·汤姆森 还是 保罗…
Like it was some kind of Paul. Thompson? Was it a Paul...
好吧 你赢了 我什么都读不出
Okay. You know what? I got nothin'.
- 不过很近了 - 是吗
- Nearly though. - Was I?
是的 我舅舅名字叫 库什曼·阿米蒂
Yeah. My uncle's name was Cushman Armitage.
是吗 斯纳佛 和 库什曼·阿米蒂
Really? Snuffles and Cushman Armitage?
这就你的童年
That was your childhood?
我真心希望今晚表演能比现在这处戏精彩
I certainly hope tonight's show is gonna be better than this.
别担心 妥妥的
Don't worry. Just you wait.
拜托 你到底找到酒店房间了吗
Hey. Come on,give me some good news on a hotel room,please.
什么 不会吧
What,are you kidding me?
不是的 是马蒂·格拉斯 迪伦
No,it's Mardi Gras,Dylan.
戏院附近没有酒店了
There's nothing within sight of the theater.
等下 等等 那个傻女人跑哪里去了
Hold on a second. Hold on. Where is this woman?
嘿 终于找到你了
Hey,hey! There you are.
看到纽奥良 你就忍不住
What,the French girl doing a little sightseeing
观光旅游了
while she's in New Orleans?
你不知道这里到处都是
No. In fact,here,speaking French
法国人吗
is actually an asset.
你看到那边那个女人了吗
Do you see that woman up there?
那是玛丽 克莱尔
That's Marie Claire.
她给我们提供了个温馨的住处
And she has a lovely apartment for us.
不客气
You're welcome.
好吧
Yeah.
我们有地方住了
We got a place.
这里安排2个 另外30个人到这里
I want two each inside of here. The other 30 around here.
屋顶 小巷 阳台
Roofs,alleys,balconies.
- 随时看着骑士团 - 好的
- Eyes on The Horsemen at all times. - Yes,sir.
哇 100年前 威廉·罗宾森 改名为 程连苏
Wow,100 years ago,William Robinson took the name Chung Ling Soo
一生再也没有在公共场合说英文
and spent his entire life never speaking English in public.
另一个家伙 马克西米兰…
This other guy,Maximillian...
现在我对魔术历史课不感兴趣
I am not interested in a history lesson on magic at this moment.
你甘愿被他们占便宜 那你就去吧
If you want to keep playing into their hands,go for it.
我反正是要先搞懂他们怎么想的
I'm just trying to understand how they think.
你觉得我帮倒忙是不
You think I'm playing in their hands,do you?
万一弄巧成拙怎么办
I don't know how any of that is gonna go against this.
怎么可能 魔术会帮到他们
This what? This magic?
莱昂内尔·史瑞克
Lionel Shrike.
在公园的正中央 他叫一个人选一张牌 然后签名
In Central Park,he has a guy pick a card and sign it.
然后他走到一个有20岁的大树旁边
Then he goes to a tree that has been there 20 years.
他们看到大树中间部分
They saw the tree in half.
透过玻璃一样看到了
Inside the tree,encased in glass,
那张签了名的牌
is the card with the signature.
你说他是怎么做到的
How did he do that?
我也不知道 但是我肯定可以用科学解释
I have no idea. But I'm sure there's a logical explanation.
大厅里安排人了吗
You guys got a guy in that lobby yet?
还没有 不过我有好消息
No,but I do have some good news.
你知道阿特拉斯是个控制狂吧
Remember how Atlas is such a control freak,
他叫整组人都装了跟踪手表
he's got his whole crew on those tracking bracelets?
什么跟踪手表
What tracking bracelets?
他要每个人都带着一个
He has every member of his crew
GPS定位的手表
wearing a tracking bracelet.
这些东西都是8号通讯信道
Those bracelets are on a sub-8 flat-band.
只要阿特拉斯能跟踪他们
So as long as Atlas is tracking them...
下一个
Next.
我们的人也就可以在这
Our boys can track Atlas...
移动通讯单位里跟踪阿特拉斯
from right here in the mobile command unit.
好的 有任何进展跟我汇报
Okay,call me if you get any movement.
收到
Copy that.
迪伦 这里很漂亮吧
You are missing the big picture here,Dylan.
巴黎有个地方叫艺术桥
There is a place in Paris,Pont des Arts.
有时候 早上我就坐在长凳上
Sometimes in the mornings I sit on a bench there.
看着人们许愿
And I watch the people make a wish
然后用锁把它锁在桥上
and lock it in a lock on the bridge.
然后把钥匙扔进塞纳河
Then throw the key into the Seine.
很多人都这么做 母亲们 恋人们 老人们
All day they do this. Mothers,lovers,old men.
然后看着钥匙伴随着他们的秘密
Watching the key sink into the water
永远地沉入水底
and their secret is locked away forever.
即真实 又魔幻
Real and,at the same time,magical.
你觉得有没有可能四骑士里有第五个人
do you really think it's possible there's a fifth Horseman?
可能吧
Yeah.
(魔术揭秘 赛迪斯·布莱德利)
古埃及有一个
There is a legend of a secret order
神秘的传说
born in ancient Egypt called
正义之眼
"The Eye."
据说他们完善了魔术
It is said they perfected sleight of hand
并从法老那里窃取食物
to steal food from the Pharaohs
然后把它们给奴隶
and give it to the slaves.
至于目的是什么
Their purpose?
就是用魔法和障眼法来伸张正义
Using magic and illusion to even the scales of justice.
还会有更多的傻子排队
Are The Horsemen next
看他们的表演 相信这个美丽的神话吗
in a long line of fools to believe this myth?
他们能再次像在拉斯维加斯一样
Will they evade the rules of law
躲过科学和逻辑的法则吗
and logic like they did in Las Vegas?
他们能再次在这片土地上
Or will the dark mysticism of this Southern swampland
施展无知的魔术吗
get the better of them?
布莱德利先生 你演的好极了
Bravo,Mr. Bradley.
你要么闭嘴 要么走
Either you have a cease-and-desist,
不过我知道 你不会闭嘴
which you don't,or you should leave.
我不想看到的人 就一定会从这个世界消失
If I want something to cease or desist,it does.
休息下
Take five.
据说你最好的一期节目
According to your potential backers,
他们给你注资了250万
you stand to make 2.5 million tops from your best special.
我这儿呢 有一张支票
I have here a check
价值350万
for 3.5 million.
飞去哪里都行 我的私人飞机任你差遣
To fly away. My jet is at your disposal.
特雷斯勒 我们开门见山的说吧
Let's not kid ourselves,Mr. Tressler.
你是他们出名的幕后人
You're in this to ride them up.
我将会是让他们名声扫地的幕后黑手
I'm in it to ride them down.
我可以理解成我们协议没有达成吧
I take it that we do not have a deal.
这之中相比一定会有冲突
And therein lies our conflict.
恕我直言
Let me be blunt.
我的钱多的可以压死你
My bank account is much,much bigger than yours.
帮我的律师也都是顶尖人物
And my lawyers are much stronger.
他们的手段
And they will manacle you
多种多样
with so many injunctions.
到最后 你就只能无助的
Until you stand by,hopelessly watching
用你贪婪的小眼睛
everything that you own drain away
看着自己所有的东西 慢慢的逝去
in front of your greedy little eyes.
我这不是第一次被威胁了
This isn't the first time I've been threatened.
但我到现在还活的好好的
And I'm still here.
没错 但是你现在是第一次被我威胁
It is,however,the first time you've been threatened by me.
如果你敢做半点搅乱我投资的事
And if you do anything to sully my investment,
也就是你刚提到的 扳倒他们四个
the ride down,which you mentioned,
我保证你 后果不堪设想
will be sudden,precipitous,and measurable on the Richter scale.
你这样做会后悔的
You shouldn't have done that.
有迷信说
According to superstition,
只要有人用玩偶去发泄愤怒
one who uses a doll to enact one's own wrath,
就会有同样的愤怒带到自己身上
is likely to bring that very wrath unto himself.
你不觉得很滑稽吗
Isn't that funny?
我还以为你不相信魔法呢
And I thought you didn't believe in magic.
帮我个忙
Do me a favor.
想像一下你最刺激的一次性爱体验
Visualize your most adventurous sexualexpnence.
你个不正经的 别想着钻我脑袋里来
Stay out of my head,you perv.
那可不行 如果我不进去
Well,no,if I stay out of your head,
那我这辈子都没机会得到你
I'm never gonna get into your pants.
- 好了 - 那么我们继续来练习下
- Right. - So let's stick with this exercise.
- 这样可以帮助… - 请恕我突然登门造访
- And it helps... - Pardon the intrusion.
我前来祝你们今晚好运的
I just wanted to wish you good luck tonight.
干什么 你想在你的网站上继续曝光我们的表演
What,so you can try to expose us later on your little website?
那是应众人所需
And on demand.
- 不可能给你曝光 - 哦 是吗
- That's not gonna happen. - Oh,no?
不怕曝光 还在飞机上练习表演
Operating on a special plane because of The Eye?
我听说是个很漂亮的飞机 阳光充裕
I heard it's a lovely place. Lots of starshine and moonbeams.
让所有魔术师梦想成真
Make any magician's wish come true.
没有人料到你们
You've come a long way,
能走到今天
much further than anyone would have expected
既有成功 又有新的目标
of a bunch of wanna-hes and has-beans.
你说成功 我觉得你是在说我
If by "has-been" you're referring to me,
我真是深感荣幸
I just wanna say I'm flattered,
因为我一直以为自己是"什么都做不到"
because I always considered myself a never-was.
你不介意我稍微读一下你的心吧
Do you mind if I do a quick read on you?
当然可以
By all means.
好的 我看到一个小男孩
Okay,I'm picturing a little boy.
总想着有一天能成为魔术师
He wants to be a great magician someday.
尽管他很优秀 但是还不够
And though he's good,he's not quite good enough.
穷尽一生也只是娱乐圈最低端的人物
So he ends up at the bottom of the entertainment food chain,
被那些他触不可及的更有才能的人踩在脚下
feeding off of those who have the talent that he never did.
告诉我 很接近了吧
Tell me. Am I getting close?
等下 你走之前我给你看下
Wait. Before you go.
我新发明的魔术 有时间不
I'm working on something new. Do you have a second?
好的 随便说一张牌
Okay. Name a card.
- 红桃K - 我就知道你要说这个
- King of hearts. - Knew it.
好了
Okay.
- 在你左边的袖子里 - 是吗
- It's up your left sleeve. - Is it?
没有啊 我没这里找不到
No. No,I don't see it up there.
要不 你看下
You know,why don't you check
你胸口的口袋
your unnecessary velveteen pocket there?
就那个
Yeah.
(去死吧)
不管怎样 十分感谢您过来参观
Anyway,thank you so much for coming by,
只是这里都是聪明人才来的地方 所以…
but this is kind of a talent only area,so...
祝你好运
Break a leg.
嘿 你也别灰心
Hey,you break something,too.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
萨沃伊管理人员欢迎你们
the Savoy management welcomes you
来到今晚的精彩演出
to tonight's special performance,
四骑士团 第二弹
The Four Horsemen,Act Two.
和以往演出不一样
Unlike traditional performances,
四骑士团鼓励你们录影
The Four Horsemen encourage you to film,
叫上你们的朋友
call your friends,
随意上传 随意微博
upload,stream,and tweet the show freely.
谢谢 演出即将开始
Thank you. The show will begin in a few minutes.
表挺漂亮
Nice watch.
祖传的
It's a family heirloom.
顺便告诉你 我知道他怎么变的了
By the way,I know how he did that trick.
- 谁 - 史瑞克
- Who? - Shrike.
他14岁的时候
So,when he was 14,
他看到了公园中央那棵树上有一个洞
he saw a hole in a tree in Central Park.
他认识了一个在旋转木马工作的人
He had a guy who worked at the carousel
像平常一样找他在牌上签了一个名
sign a card for what looked like a routine little trick.
然后呢
And?
那个人退休之后 也就是18年后
At the guy's retirement,18 years later,
伯劳去那里表演了 要之前那个人又签了次名
Shrike performs,has the guy sign a card,
然后"嗖"一下
and presto!
牌就进到树里去了
The card is in the tree.
其实 卡早在18年前就已经在树里了
It was in the tree for 18 years.
牌在树里面
The card was in the tree.
跟着树一起长了18年
The tree grew around the card in 18 years.
我是说 这根本不是魔法 不是魔术
I mean,that isn't magic. It's not magic.
关键是 这个戏法就是不能近距离观看
The point is,the trick was not to look closely.
要远观 甚至是年代上的久远
It was to look so far
以至于能看到过去的20年
that you see 20 years into the past.
史瑞克淹死之后 没有人找到他的尸体
After Shrike drowned,they never found the body.
你的意思是
What are you suggesting?
亚瑟·特雷斯特 为您带来
Arthur Tressler presents
杰克·怀尔德
Jack Wilder,
亨利·里夫斯
Henley Reeves,
梅里特·麦金尼
Merritt McKinney,
以及丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
and Daniel Atlas.
有请我们的四骑士
The Four Horsemen.
谢谢 在我们开始前
Thank you. Before we begin,
我们今晚将把精彩的演出呈现给
we'd like to single out two people in particular.
一男一女
A man and a woman to
两个特殊的人
whom we'd like to dedicate tonight's performance.
FBI 特工迪伦
FBI Agent Dylan Rhodes
以及可爱的 没经验的
and the lovely,if somewhat inexperienced,
国际刑警特工艾尔玛德雷 掌声 各位
Interpol Agent Alma Dray,everyone.
是的 罗兹特工发誓说要抓到我们
Yeah,Agent Rhodes has personally vowed to "nail us."
如果他有那个能耐 当然我们也非常欢迎
And we encourage him to do so if he has the brains and the fur.
魔术是什么
What is magic?
就我们看来 只是障眼法
Our argument,nothing but targeted deception.
所以请仔细看
So I want you to look.
越近越好
Look as closely as possible.
因为接下来你们将看到的表演
Because the tricks you are about to see
看似毫无联系
may not seem connected.
但我保证 一定紧密相关
But we assure you,they are.
到底是七十二变呢
Is what follows 100 different tricks?
还是一个幻觉
Or is it one giant illusion?
现在 我们带来的是一个非常老的魔术
And now for one of the oldest tricks in the book.
丹尼 麻烦把盒子打开
Danny,if you wouldn't mind opening up the box,
给大家展示一下 里面空空如也
and showing everybody that it's completely empty.
现在 我们要请12位勇敢的观众
Now,we're gonna need 12 courageous volunteers.
现在我把这小家伙
I'm gonna take sweet little Fluffy here,
放进这个神秘的盒子
and put her inside this mystery box.
观众席有两支铅笔
There are two pencils out there.
麻烦举高 让我看看
Hold 'em up high. Let me see 'em.
- 这里 - 好的
- Here! - Yeah!
现在 说一个很有魔力的词
And now,you will say the magic word.
麻里麻里哄
Abracadabra.
很好 现在我挥动一下这个魔棒
Yes,and I will wave this magic wand
虽然没有用 然后…
for no reason. And then...
小兔子在众目睽睽之下凭空消失了
Fluffy has magically vanished before your very eyes.
如果你们没体验过集体催眠
If you haven't experienced mass hypnosis,
现在就有机会了
you're about to.
睡吧
And sleep.
睡吧 沉睡吧 睡吧 …
Down,down. Sleep,sleep. Completely sleep.
睡吧 好的 睡吧
Good,good. Sleep,sleep.
今晚我们将揭秘一些
And now we are gonna debunk
神秘的魔术
a few magic myths this evening.
我们都知道那只小兔子肯定没死
We all know that Fluffy is,in fact,alive and well.
但是又奇蹟般的出现了
And Fluffy has miraculously appeared.
由于镜子的关系
As has the mirror
盒子无论如何看起来都是空的
which makes the box only appear as though it's empty.
当你们听到"不许动"这个词的时候
When you hear the word "freeze"
你们就都变成了橄榄球员
you are all football players.
你们的任务就是擒住 摔倒
And your job is to tackle,
卸球
dismantle,
压倒
crush,
撕扯
tear limb from limb,
四分卫
the quarterback.
我们都看过从帽子里变出兔子
Now,we've all heard of pulling the rabbit out of the hat.
但有人看过把兔子变成帽子吗
But has anyone heard of pulling a hat out of a rabbit?
你们等下就会知道谁是四分卫了
You will know who the quarterback is.
四分卫等下会说出 我告诉你们的单词"不准动"
He will be the one saying that word. Freeze.
三 二 一
Three,two,one...
把手放到中间来 一 二 三…
Put your hands in the middle. One,two,three...
干掉四分卫
Kill the quarterback!
回到你们的座位区
Get on back to your seats.
我有预感马上就会见到你们
I got a feeling I'm gonna be seeing you soon.
我感觉你轻了不少
I guess you have lost some weight.
在休息的时候
At the intermission,
我们要你们把银行卡的余额都写在了纸上
we asked you to write down your current bank balance,
然后封在信封里
and seal it in an envelope.
现在是时候拿出信封了
Now it's time to take those envelopes out.
都拿出来吧
Everyone take 'em out.
现在请所有人
Now,everybody,
大声的喊出你们自己的名字 一起喊…喊吧
shout out your name. All at once. Go.
喊出声
Shout 'em out.
克莱门特 佛兰尼克
Clement? Frannick?
- 对 我在这儿 - 哦 在后排
- Yeah! Up here! - Oh. Way up there.
好的 蒂娜 罗伯森
Okay. Dina? Robertson?
是我
That's me!
好的 喊出自己名字 喊吧
Okay. Names. Names. Let's go.
希基 约瑟法
Josepha Hickey?
是我
That's me!
约瑟法 我要你集中精力想着你的余额
Josepha,I want you to focus on your balance,
然后大声从1数到10
and count from one to 10 out loud.
一 二 三 四 五…
One,two,three,four,five...
停
Stop.
你的余额第一位是5吗
Is the first digit 5?
是的
Yes.
再来一次 这次快点
Do it again. This time,faster.
一 二 三 四 五 六
One,two,three,four,five,six...
停
Stop.
六 再数次
Six. Again.
一 二
One,two...
约瑟法 你今天账户余额是562吗
Josepha,is your bank balance $562 as of today?
是的 我就这么多
Yeah. That's what I got.
不好意思 你错了
Unfortunately,you're wrong.
好了 蒂娜
Okay,Dina,
一
四
七
- 是7 - 对的
- 7. - Yeah.
你觉得你对了 但是你错了
You think it is. But in fact,you,too,are wrong.
克莱门特
Clement.
你账户余额不是6500
You do not have $6,500 in your account.
实际上 所有人起立
In fact,everybody stand up. Everybody.
好的 把信封举到额头上
Yeah. Put your envelopes to your forehead.
集中精力想着余额数字
Focus on your number.
这太…我也怕发生这样的事 天呐
This is... Oh,dear. Just as I feared.
太奇怪了
Oh,this is strange.
你知道吗 很不好意思 你们都错了
You know,I hate to say this,but you're all wrong.
关于自己银行余额有多少
Every last one of you is dead wrong
你们全都搞错了
about what you think is in your account.
好了 你们可以坐下了
Okay,you can sit down now.
哦 我差点忘记了
Yeah. I almost forgot.
今晚要不是投资商特雷斯特
This evening would not be possible
我们也不可能有这个演出的机会
if it weren't for our great benefactor Arthur Tressler.
热烈鼓掌 热烈欢迎
Big applause! Big applause!
阿特 就算是为了最后几处演出
Art,actually,why don't you come up on stage
也有劳你也过来下吧
for the finale?
- 下来吧 阿特 - 下来 阿特
- Come on down,Art! - Come on down,Art!
他来了 很好
There he goes. Okay,good.
安排妥善了吗
Are we on red?
妥妥的 全员待命
Bright red. We're all standing by.
很好 封锁现场 不允许任何人出入
All right,no one leaves the theater. No one.
他来了
There he goes.
阿特 你填了你自己的信封吗
Now,Art,did you fill out your envelope?
好吧 不用了 我们帮你准备好了
Well,no need. We've done it for you.
阿特 让我猜猜
Now,Art,I took a guess.
140以上 对吗
North of 140. Am I right?
顺便说下 是1.4亿
That's 140 million,by the way.
对不起 梅里特
I'm sorry,Merritt.
他的余额为什么是正确的
How can he be right about his balance
而其他人的都发生错误了
and everyone else be wrong?
我觉得有可能是 他的 也错了
I think possibly because he,too,is wrong.
请所有人拿出那张纸
Everybody,take out your paper.
用座位底的手电
And using the flashlight under your seat,
照亮你们那张纸
start to warm up that paper.
然后你们正确的余额就会慢慢浮现
I think your correct balance begins to appear.
阿特 你先别担心 我们也给你准备了一个手电
Now,Art,don't worry,we have a flashlight for you.
好的
Yes.
看着
Look.
丹尼尔什么情况
What's going on there,Daniel?
等下 这真奇怪 一秒前还是…
Wait. This is weird. A second ago,it said
144,579,651美元
$144,579,651.
而现在
But now...
少了 70,000美元
Now it says $70,000 less.
约瑟法麻烦你站起来
Josepha,can you stand up?
好的
Yes.
你新的余额是多少
Now,what is your new number?
现在有70,562在我账上
$70,562 now in my account.
有没有可能是因为 阿特的钱变到了
Is it possible that Josepha's balance went up
约瑟法的账户里
the exact amount that Art's went down?
嘿 快看 又一次减少了
Hey. Check it out. It's happening again.
是吗
IS it?
哦 真的
Wow. It is.
阿特的余额又少了280,000美元
Art's balance has gone down another 280K.
蒂娜 罗伯斯 你的余额是多少来着
Dina Robertson? What did yours say?
281,477美元
$281,477.
我们承认我们错了
We have a confession to make.
她说的对 我们撒谎了
She's right. We lied about something.
是的 你们都不是随机抽选的
Yes. None of you were chosen at random.
你们都有一个共同点
All of you have one thing in common.
你们所有人都是经济危机时期的受害者
Everyone in this room was a victim
在曾经辉煌的城市里
of the hard times that hit one of America's most treasured cities.
一个个失去了你们的房子 你们的车
Some of you lost your houses,your cars.
生意倒闭
Your businesses.
失去了你们爱的人
Your loved ones.
但是你们所有人都投保了同一家公司
But all of you were insured by the same company.
特雷斯勒保险公司
Tressler Insurance.
你们被抛弃了
You were abandoned.
保险公司钻各种空子
You were loopholed...
不给予赔偿
...out of your settlements.
这些都是表演 不是真的吧
This is all for show. Correct?
你说的"这些"是指 当着这么多观众和在舞台上吗
"All" meaning we're doing it onstage in front of a paying audience?
- 这样的话 那我回答 是的 为了表演 - 哇 哇
- Then,yes,it's for show. - Whoa! Whoa!
我银行账户里有82,000美元了
I've got $82,000 in my bank account!
我刚手机收到银行短信说的
It says it right here on my cell phone!
所有人快看你们的手机
Everybody,look at your cell phones right now! Everybody!
这都是真的吗
Is this for real?
我不知道
I don't know.
又偷到了吗
Is this happening?
我也不知道 说不定
I don't know! I can't tell!
嘿 是你干的吗
Hey! Did you do this?
怎么可能是我们 阿特
How could we,Art?
我们又没有你的密码
We don't have your password.
我们也想知道你的私人信息
We'd need access to information
但却无从着手
we could never get our hands on.
你的密保 比如
Yes,security questions,for instance,like,
你妈妈的中间名字 我也不知道
I don't know,your mother's maiden name
或者你第一个宠物的名字
or the name of your first pet.
你说我们怎么可能知道 阿特
Where would we get that information,Art?
你肯定不会告诉我们的
You certainly would never tell us.
收到确认 确实偷到了 他们刚打劫了他
We got confirmation. It's really happening. They robbed him.
别让他们逃了
Do not let them get away.
别担心 飞机和车留给你了
Hey,we left you the jet and the Rolls.
你们会付出惨重代价的
You got hell to pay!
站住
Stop!
站住 所有人都别动
Stop! Nobody move!
不许动
Freeze!
四分卫
Quarterback!
我们是四骑士团
We are The Four Horsemen.
各位晚安
Good night.
把他们推开
Get 'em off me!
滚开 都下去
Get off! Get off me!
放开我
Get off me!
听着 所有这条街上的人注意
All right. I want everyone on the street! Everyone!
- 四分卫 - 四分卫
- Quarterback! - Quarterback!
富勒 在戏院门口等我
Fuller,meet me in front of the theater
带上跟踪器
and bring the tracker.
快走 快点
Let's go! Let's go! Now! Come on! Let's go!
跟踪器给我
Give me the tracker.
出发了
Let's go.
FBI 让开
FBI! Clear!
- 迪伦 - 混蛋
- Dylan! - Damn.
有什么发现
What have you got?
跟着红点 他就在那里
That's him right there. Follow the red dot.
好的 我带着这个 包抄他们 断掉他们后路
All right,I'll take this. Go. Box 'em. Cut 'em off that way.
他在勃艮第大街左转了
He's turning left on Burgundy.
嘿 让开
Hey! Move!
让开 让开
Move! Move!
我看到他朝北走了
I got him heading north on Bourbon.
- 不好意思 快让开 - 嘿
- Sorry. Move,move! - Hey!
嘿 借过快让 借过
Hey,excuse me. Move,move! Excuse me.
我跟丢了
I've lost him at Bourbon.
混蛋 你在哪里？
Damn! Where are you?
借过
Excuse me.
他正朝交易所跑去
He's heading south on Exchange Place.
站住
Stop!
你犯什么傻呢
What are you doing?
他进拿破仑小区了
He's going in Napoleon House.
让开 让开
Move! Move!
快让开
Move out of the way!
嘿
Hey!
让开
Move!
他在厕所 我抓到他了
He's in the bathroom. I have him in the bathroom.
不 不 不
No!No!No!
不许动
Freeze!
放下你的武器
Lower your weapons!
什么
What?
我一直在跟踪自己
I'm tracking myself!
四骑士他们把追踪器放到
The Horsemen left egg on the face of what they call
他们嘴里所说的新手特工身上了
the alphabet agencies,
FBI的能力问题
calling into question
遭到了质疑
the efficacy of the FBI's task force
以及这单案子的负责人
as well as the man in charge of the investigation,
迪伦
Special Agent Dylan Rhodes,
该特工被当众取笑
who was publicly ridiculed,
甚至参与了今晚的表演
and even tackled at tonight's performance.
说他弄巧成拙
Talk about a fumble.
这个笑话瞬间传遍了全国
This is quickly becoming a national story,
看起来四骑士在这几天的时间里
as The Horsemen have now seemingly pulled off the impossible
又一次带来了奇蹟
for the second time in as many days.
而仅在两晚前 四骑士
Two nights ago in Vegas,The Horsemen
成功障眼 偷走了巴黎一家银行的钱
seemingly robbed a bank in Paris...
嘿
Hey.
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
我在喝闷酒
I'm having a drink.
我来接你的
I came to get you.
我很担心你
I'm worried about you.
你担心我 好吧 应该是我担心你
You're worried about me. Well,I'm worried about you.
你有机会瞄准阿特拉斯的
Atlas. You had him.
但是他没有武器
He didn't have a weapon.
我不能就这样开枪 你自己清楚
I couldn't shoot him and you know that.
是 但是你却让他走了
Yeah,but you... You let him go.
不是吗
Didn't you?
一个法国妹子无端端跑出来
A pretty French girl shows up out of the blue,
故意假装好像是我的搭档 然后让逃犯跑掉了
acts like she's my partner and then she lets the bad guy go?
放开我的手
Let go of my arm.
你到底是谁
Who exactly are you anyway?
我记得好像 你说你是个文职啊
I thought you said you were a desk agent.
还不错
Not bad.
这是什么
What is this?
什么是荷鲁斯之眼
What's the Eye of Horus?
今晚我什么都不想说
Oh,certainly nothing I want to get into tonight.
等你清醒了再跟我说
You're dismissive enough about me when you're sober.
自己找回家的路吧
Find your way back yourself.
布莱德利先生 特雷斯勒想请你喝一杯
Mr. Bradley? Mr. Tresslerwould like you to join him for a drink.
先生 你的
Sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
你跟他们到底什么关系
What is your role with them?
关系
Role?
是的 你好像很清楚他们的一言一行
Yes. You seem to know everything about them.
他们要去哪里 他们要干什么
What they're gonna do. Where they're gonna be.
如果这样想能舒服点的话
If it makes you feel any better,
这跟你都没关系 不要自责
this wasn't about you.
那你告诉我 为什么都跟我没有关系
Please tell me why this was not about me.
特雷斯勒先生 这些都是魔术小把戏
This is a magic trick,Mr. Tressler.
只是大规模的
Played out on a global scale.
而你 只是个棋子
You,sir,are the abracadabra.
他们设下陷阱 是用来娱乐的
The distraction,while they set up the real trick.
我的1.4亿用来娱乐
I was a $140-million distraction?
是的
Yes.
正是你这种自大 让你一开始就陷入了他们的圈套
And that very ego that got you involved with them in the first place
你一直觉得
is what keeps you from seeing that.
- 你知道的… - "我可以轻松让你消失"
- You know... - "I can destroy you."
是的 我知道
Yes,I do know.
但 你不会
Well,you won't.
你不会扳倒他们
And you won't destroy them.
不管这个把戏如何
Whatever this grand trick is,
毕竟也是好久之前就设计好的
it was designed a long time ago.
我坚信接下来发生的更令人惊讶
And I believe that what's about to follow is really going to amaze.
所以我建议你 坐在前排的位置 慢慢的观看吧
So I suggest you sit back and enjoy your front row seat.
毕竟你付了1.4亿门票
You paid quite a lot of good money for it.
无论你曝光他们要多少钱
Whatever you stand to make
我都双倍付给你
I'll double it,if you expose them now.
我要你扳倒他们 曝光他们
And destroy them.
我说五百万
I stand to make five million.
我会退缩吗
Am I flinching?
你不会的
No,you're not.
(何露斯的监护人)
嘿
Hey.
对不起 昨天把你压在桌子上
I'm sorry for your arm.
应该是我道歉才对
No. I'm sorry.
我是个混蛋 当时我喝醉了
I was an asshole. I was drunk.
我太失落了
I'm at a loss.
你知道 梅里特他是对的 说我几乎没离开过书桌
You know,when Merritt said I hardly spent any time away from the desk,he was right.
我只是个调研人员 这才是我的专业
I'm a researcher. That's what I do best.
那么 这东西都说什么
So what's this all about?
据推测 如果你相信的话
Supposedly,if you buy into it,
正义之眼就是
The Eye are the keepers
魔法的先祖
of real magic
它会保护练习真正魔法的人
and the protectors of those who practice it.
入会的候选人
"Candidates for initiations
必须服从一系列的考验
"must follow a series of commands with blind obedience."
- 这不可能 - 但有人相信是真的
- This isn't real. - But there are some who think it is.
能给我下不
May I?
根据这里所说 两个世纪才会重新选一次人
According to this,they only take new people twice a century.
那又如何 四骑士所做的事情就是为了通过测验
So what? The Horsemen are doing these shows in order to get into this thing?
- 我不知道 - 我不知道
- I don't know. - I don't know.
我意思是 我猜如果不是的话 这些人可以直接偷银行
I mean,I guess these guys could just rob banks to rob banks.
没必要表演出来
They don't have to put on a show for that.
也有可能真的只是个神话
It's probably just a myth.
但是 这完全不符合逻辑 而且我觉得逻辑科学也无法解释
But it doesn't make any sense,and I don't think logic will solve this for us.
- 你怎么知道 - 我不清楚
- You don't say? - No.
我觉得有些东西
Ibefieve that some things are only discovered
向前迈进一大步才能明白
if you take certain leaps.
- 好的 我该走… - 好的 没问题
- Well,I gotta get to... - Yeah. Yeah.
- 谢谢 晚安 - 你也是 晚安
- Thanks. Good night. - Yeah. Good night.
- 不好意思 - 没事
- Sorry. - It's all right.
如果荷鲁斯之眼真的有 我们必须假设他们正监视着我们 是吧
If The Eye did exist,we'd have to assume they were watching us,right?
混蛋
Shit.
我觉得有人监视我们 但是绝对不是魔法
I think someone is watching us,but it isn't magic.
你猜测是对的 这根本就不是你的手机
Your fears are correct. This is not and has never been your phone.
是照你手机样子做出来的 除了安装了这个
It's a clone in every way,except for this.
漏洞
A bug.
有人在监听你每一个电话和短信
Someone has heard every call,read every text.
这就是他们如何总能提前猜到我们的行动
That's how they were able to stay ahead of us.
混蛋
God damn it!
去拿阿特拉斯的审问录影过来
Get me Atlas' interrogation tape.
是的 长官 我硬碟上有
Yes,sir. I have it on the hard drive.
有图像了
Picture's up.
好的 快进
Okay,fast forward.
继续 继续 停住
Go on,go on. Freeze!
好的 一帧帧的快进 继续
Okay. Frame by frame. Go on.
播放
Play it through.
停 放大点
Stop. Zoom in tighter. Tighter.
就那里 那就是他如何偷天换日的
There. That's where he took my phone.
那个东西还在发送消息吗
Is that thing transmitting?
不 只有你打电话和短信的时候才会
Only when you're making a call or sending a text.
再加上我已经拿出来了
Plus I removed the bug.
好的 把他放回去
All right. Put it back in and turn on the phone.
他们不知道 我们知道了
They don't know that we know about the bug.
这样以来 反而我们领先他们一步
As of this instant,we are ahead of them.
我们还要假装和不知道一样 懂吗
We need to keep it that way. Understand?
找到我自己原本的手机 跟踪它
Find my real phone and track it.
已经跟踪了 20分钟前在纽约
Already did. As of about 20 minutes ago,it's in New York City.
很好
Good.
切断他们所有供给
I wanna cut 'em off at the knees.
他们的电 断掉
They got power? Cut it.
手机 电力 水 全部断掉
They got phones,electricity,water? Cut it.
榨干他们
Squeeze 'em out.
我要他们感觉到我们的存在
I want 'em to feel our presence.
给我安排飞机
And get me an airplane!
防火墙崩溃 他们知道了吗
The firewall's down. Do they know about this?
他们是指谁
They who?
他们 就是 就是我们上面的人
"They," "them," whoever we're working for.
我们上面是谁
Who are we working for?
我们准备好坐牢了吗
And are we prepared to go to jail for them?
别自乱阵脚了
Stop being paranoid.
但确实来抓我们了
It really does happen.
那只是抓你 没说要抓我们
It happened to you. Doesn't mean it's gonna happen to us.
大家看下能不能这样
Guys,I don't know if can do this,all right.
我可不想坐牢 你知道吗
I don't want to go to jail,you know?
那就别搞砸了 你一直说想被
Then don't screw up. You're always talking about
当成年人一样看待
wanting to be treated like an adult.
那现在就表现的像个成年人一样
Now might be a good time to start acting like one.
严格按照计划执行 在这待着 烧掉所有东西
Stick to the plan. Stay here and burn it all.
我都不知道我在干什么
I don't know what I'm doing here.
那你在别的地方又能干什么
I don't know what you would do anywhere else.
我一直等着熬出头
I'm here for the pot of gold at the end of the rainbow.
就这样了 我走了
That's it. Then I'm gone.
等这一切都结束了 你想干什么都行
You can do whatever you want when this is over,Merritt.
但在那之前 按计划来
But until then,you stick to the plan.
各位 条子来了
Hey,guys. They're here.
- 我的人准备好了 - 那快点出发吧
- My guys are ready to go. - Let's do this quickly...
- 不 - 什么
- No. - What?
她没有权利
She doesn't have jurisdiction here.
她跟我一起的 国际刑警
She's Interpol. She's with me.
她留这里
She stays.
什么 你说什么
What? What?
在车里待着
Stay in the car.
走吧
Let's go.
快点 出发了
Okay. Let's do it.
联邦调查局
FBI!
女士优先
Ladies first.
别动
Don't move!
告诉我
Tell me.
我的钱用对地方了吧
Is my money being well-spent?
那必须的
Exceedingly well.
那我问你
Now you tell me,
你想怎么解决他们呢
how do you like your Horsemen?
是做炖肉丁还是油炸
Fricasseed or fried?
剁碎吧
Shredded.
我会跟大厨说的
I'll tell the Chef.
别动
Freeze!
迪伦
Dylan!
等等
Hold on!
你这…
You little...
过来
Come here!
5号安全 6号待命
Five is clear. Standing by for six.
- 该死的 - 该死的
- You little Shit! - You little Shit!
- 你在耍什么把戏 - 你在耍什么把戏
- What game are you playing? - What game are you playing?
6号安全 过去7号
We're all good at six. Move to seven.
收到 去7号 快 快 快
Copy that. Going to seven. Go,go,go!
不要 不要 回去
No,no,no,no,no. Go back!
嘿
Hey!
这边
Come here!
好…好…等等…等等
All right,hold on,hold on!
- 真的吗 - 对啊
- Really? - Yup.
你…
You...
你这…
You little...
该死的
Shit!
快给我
Give me that!
各单位注意 包围北边出口
All units,cover the north exit now!
埃文这边安全
Clear on Evan.
堵住所有可能的出口
Block every possible exit.
喂 别走 混蛋
Hey! Get back. Shit.
- 联邦调查局 算是吧 我要用你的车 谢谢 - 什么？
- FBI. Sort of. I need your car. Thanks. - What?
什么
What?
停下来 停下来
Stop! Stop!
喂
Hey!
很好 跟着他
Good. Follow him!
不要再跟我说什么待在车里 再也别
Don't ever tell me to stay in the car. Ever.
我没有战术指挥权
I didn't have tactical command.
如果你不相信我 直接告诉我就好了
If you don't trust me,just tell me.
向我保证 下次 你会支持我
Promise me,next time,you will back me up.
我们能迟点讨论这个问题吗 拜托了
Could we have this conversation later,please?
不行
No!
好好好…我向你保证 走 马上
Okay,fine,I promise. Now,go!
- 他们去哪了 - 他们在哪
- Where'd they go? - Where are they?
我不知道 她刚刚征用了别人的车
I don't know. She just took some guy's car.
- 他们在哪 - 那条路 那条路
- Where are they? - That way. That way.
- 那是你的车吗 - 是的
- Is that your car? - Yeah.
我们走
Let's go.
他在那里
There he is!
快点
Move!
转左
Left!
我们在罗斯福路的东边
We're heading east on the FDR Drive.
- 这不是东边 - 是北边 北边
- This is not east. - North! North!
- 我们在罗斯福路的北边 - 什么啊
- We're heading north on the FDR Drive. - What?
我们正向罗斯福路上方过去
We're coming to you live above the FDR,
纽约警察局和联邦特工
where NYPD and federal agents,as you now see,
正在高速追击一部
are engaged in a high-speed pursuit,
黑色轿车
following a black sedan.
富勒 你在那里
Fuller,where are you?
就在这 正在你屁股后面
Right here. Trying to catch up to you now.
我们在找一个更好的射击点
We're now trying to get you a better shot.
快点
Come on!
他们好像在转向
It looks like they're turning
是去59号大桥路
onto the 59th Street Bridge.
一旦他们在范围内
As soon as we have them within range,
我们会转播你实时情况
we will bring you those pictures live.
很好 继续跟着他
Good. Just stay with him.
快快快
Go,go,go!
小心点 你在巴士后面
Behind... You're behind the bus!
超过去
Get over!
该死的
Oh,shit!
这边
Come here!
退后 别过来
Get back! Get back!
迪伦 走 我们走
Dylan,let's go,man!
快点 你…
Come on,you...
- 快点 快走 - 他要死在里面了
- Come on,man! Get out! - He's gonna die in here.
别管他了 你又不能做什么
Leave him! There's nothing you can do!
我们快走 别管他了
Let's go! Leave him!
- 那张纸 - 迪伦
- The Paper! - Dylan!
快 快走 我们快走
Let's go! Let's go! Come on!
今天 大受欢迎且存争议的魔术团
Today,the unfolding story of a popular and controversial group of magicians,
很快就捕获了人心
who have been fast capturing the public's imagination,
但一场从唐人街开始的追捕
took a dark turn when a police action that began in Chinatown
演变成高速公路追击
developed into a dramatic,high-speed chase across the 59th Street Bridge,
最终造成致命的车祸并夺去了杰克·怀尔德的生命
which caused a fatal collision that took the life of Jack Wilder,
他正是所谓的"四骑士团"其中之一
one of the so-called Four Horsemen.
至于其他3个骑士现在仍下落不明
The whereabouts of the other three Horsemen remain unknown at this time.
迪伦 他们刚研究出杰克车里的那张纸是什么了
Dylan,they just figured out what the paper was in Jack's car.
那他们知道是什么了
So they know what it is?
还有为什么他宁愿死也要保护那张纸
And why the kid died trying to protect it.
埃文 正在路上 很快就过来向我们汇报了
Evans is on his way to brief us right now.
我们走
Let's go.
你一定想先拿着这个吧
You're gonna wanna take this first,though.
为什么
What's that?
你朋友赛迪斯·布莱德利打的
Your friend Thaddeus Bradley.
罗兹
Rhodes.
你不知道这神奇的助理
You do understand the function
是干什么的吧 罗兹警官
of the magician's assistant,don't you,Agent Rhodes?
知道啊 她能在魔术师变戏法时
Yeah,she's there to distract them
分散观众的注意力
while he sets up the trick.
大错特错
You'd be right if you weren't so wrong.
当你在看魔术师表演时
While you're watching the magician,
看似无辜的助理正在牵线搭桥
that lovely innocent is actually pulling the strings.
你没觉得奇怪吗 国际刑警为什么要
Don't you find it peculiar that Interpol would send you
一个新人来帮你
a first timer off the desk to be your assistant?
为什么她要求接手这一单案子来
Why did she request to be put on the case?
她是被派遣过来的
She was assigned to the case.
天命难违啊
Luck of the draw.
就像要你从牌堆里抽一张一样
Like choosing a random card in the deck.
我发现奇怪的地方了 你怎么突然这么大方了
I find it odd,your sudden act of generosity.
你有什么好处
What's in it for you?
只是想让这场争斗公平点
Just trying to even the game.
我怎么觉得我在对牛弹琴
I feel like I'm playing with somebody wearing ankle weights and flippers.
聪明点 罗兹
Keep up,Agent Rhodes. Keep up.
我们有麻烦了
We got a problem.
那是保险箱
Here's the safe.
不 不 不 嘿
No,no,no. Hey.
他在这干嘛
What's he doing here?
给我们条线索
Giving us our first solid lead.
我们在过去五年里调查了
We've been investigating a private security contractor
一个叫埃尔克霍恩
called Elkhorn
- 的私家安保 - 然后呢
- for the last five years. - And?
他们藏了差不多50亿美元
They've been hiding close to a half billion dollars...
我没问你 我问他
I didn't ask you. I asked him.
那些钱在女王路的一间仓库里的保险箱里
The money's in a vault inside a warehouse in Queens.
我觉得这个保险箱就是他们魔术师的终极目标
We think this vault is your magicians' final target.
你从刚刚死在桥上那个魔术师
The magician who died on the bridge...
快要烧焦的手里拿到了埃尔克霍恩的机密文件
You pulled our classified Elkhorn file right from his crispy little hand.
以及他们有些什么扯淡花招
And despite their bullshit Robin Hood razzle-dazzle,
那些魔术师跟贼没什么区别
your magicians are nothing more than common thieves.
他们是怎么拿到文件的
How did they get the file?
罗兹警官 这你应该再清楚不过了
This is the part you're gonna find particularly interesting,Agent Rhodes.
他们利用你手机上的远程代码
They patched to my server after they accessed
骇了你的移动指挥中心之后
your mobile command center in New Orleans
又骇进了我的伺服器
with codes they got from your phone.
当时 是你要我们全部出去追他们的
You ordered us all out to chase after them.
你这不专业的程度表现得
The level of incompetence displayed on this case,
就已经很像是魔术了
that's a magic trick in and of itself.
"麻里麻里哄"我来接管了
Abracadabra. I'm taking over.
老大 他要接管
Boss,he's taking over?
我们走
Let's go,gentlemen.
嘿 我有话跟你说
Hey. I want to have a word with you.
不要再那样跟我说话了
Don't ever talk to me like that again.
- 你为什么要接这个案子 - 什么
- Why the hell did you take this case? - What?
人们说我"人心难懂"这是美国人的说法
People say I'm "hard to read." That's an American expression.
你明白吗
Do you understand it?
明白
Yes.
很好 那就让我向你明确地说清楚
Good,then let me make myself perfectly clear to you.
如果我发现你不是你口口声声
If I find out that you are anything other than
所说的身份 我发誓…
who you say you are,I swear...
法国人也有这么个词
And we French also have an expression.
"愚公移山"
"Faith can move mountains."
我们要想抓到四骑士团
If we hope to capture The Horsemen,
那你得相信我
then you need to have a little faith in me.
我完全没必要害你
Because I've done nothing to deserve otherwise.
我刚被数落了一番
I just got my ass handed to me.
这个案子已经不归我管了
I am losing this case.
我没多少时间了 信念太奢侈
So faith is a luxury I don't have any time for right now.
杰克想成为最有名的魔术师
More than anything in his life,
比他生命中的任何事都重要
Jack wanted to be the most famous magician who ever lived.
我不能说他已经做到了
And I can't say he achieved it,
但是我真心希望 有他的地方都充满了魔力
but I do hope wherever he is,it is full of magic.
但关键是…抱歉
But the point is... Sorry.
关键是…
The point is...
人在江湖 身不由己
The point of why we are here is to say that we are not... We cannot quit now.
我们已经着手一件比我们本身更重要的事了
We've started something bigger than all of us.
我们一定要把它做完
We have to finish it.
靠近仓库中
Approaching the warehouse.
5号和6号队分别掩护北门和南门入口
Units 5 and 6 cover the north and south entrances.
我们现在就去地下室
We are going for the vault.
喂 保险箱呢 保险箱呢
Hey. Where's the safe? Where's the safe?
这是什么
What is this?
这该死的保险箱去哪了
Where the hell is the goddamn safe?
你们刚在外面的时候就已经搬出去了
We just moved it while you were outside.
- 埃文的命令 - 什么
- Evans' orders. - What?
我从没说过啊
I never said that.
先生 你打了电话
Sir,you got a phone call
还说"华盛顿"想搬走保险箱
and said Washington wants the safe moved.
我绝对没有说
You never heard that come out of my mouth,Agent.
这是怎么回事
What happened?
你告诉我这是怎么回事 这简直是扯淡
You tell me what's going on,because this is bullshit!
别这样
No!
天啊
Jesus Christ.
你这是在干什么
Sir? Sir? What are you doing?
应该是贝多芬的 D大调协奏曲
I think it's Beethoven's Concerto in D-Major.
保险箱呢
Where's the safe?
他们正在装上货车
His team is loading the truck.
- 嘿 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey! Hey! - Hey!
- 拦住货车 - 别走
- Stop the truck! - Stop!
- 别走 - 嘿 拦住货车
- Stop! - Hey! Stop that truck!
这是怎么回事啊 我们还有任务呢
What the hell's going on? We got our orders.
现在你有新的任务了 把它打开
Now you've got new orders. Open it up.
听好 我是这样想的
Okay. Here's what I want.
现在 他们以为这保险箱已经送走了
At this moment,they think that safe's leaving this site.
那我们就跟着它吧
So we stay with it.
我们跟着它去…这是去哪的
We follow it all the way to... Where's it going?
女王街5号 在大街的那头
5 Pointz. Up the street.
那我们去女王街5号吧 保险箱去哪我们就去哪
So we go to 5 Pointz. Wherever the safe goes,we go.
它能带我们去到他们那儿
It'll lead us right to 'em.
你们俩跟我
You two are with me.
伙计们
Guys.
看 局里打电话来了
Look. Office just called with this.
20分钟前四骑士团传到YouTube上的
Horsemen posted it to YouTube 20 minutes ago.
人在江湖…
The point of why we're here is to say that we are not...
身不由己
We cannot quit now.
我们已经着手于一件比我们本身更重要的事了
We've started something bigger than all of us.
我们一定要把它做完
We have to finish it.
当你们看到我们时 记住杰克·怀尔德这个名字
Remember the name Jack Wilder when you see us live,
我们7点到女王街5号
5 Pointz,Queens,7:00.
他们的表演还有30分钟就开始了
Their show is in a half an hour.
而那正是我们要去的地方
It's exactly where we're headed.
我不知道啊 老大 虽然我不想唱反调
I don't know,boss. I don't wanna be the naysayer,
但不得不说 这些家伙太狡猾了
but these guys are kinda tricky.
罗兹 他们只是搞娱乐的
Rhodes,they're entertainers.
今晚女王街5号 将让您头晕目眩
A stunning turnout here in 5 Pointz
戏弄FBI的魔术团四骑士 将带来最后压轴大戏
as the renegade Horsemen taunt the FBI into a final showdown.
骑士团诚邀大家观看他们最后一出戏
The Horsemen have invited us to their final round
也是三人面向FBI的最后一站
of their three-act face-off with the FBI.
他们还有什么身藏绝技呢 今晚就来探个究竟吧
What do they have in store? We're about to find out.
仔细监控那部货车 看看有谁接近
All eyes on the truck. Let's see who approaches.
收到
Copy that.
罗兹警官 富勒
Agents Rhodes,Fuller?
说吧
Go,for us.
这边有动静 有人向货车走去
We've got movement. Someone's walking toward the truck.
是个女的
It's a woman.
- 别动 - 该死的
- Freeze! - Oh,shit!
这是怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
喂 他是电视上那家伙
Hey! It's the guy from the TV.
放下你的枪
Put your guns down.
瞧瞧这是谁啊 第五骑士啊
Look who it is. The fifth Horseman.
你在开玩笑吧
Are you kidding?
我在跟着他们 跟你一样
I'm following them,just like you are.
我没有跟踪任何人
I'm not following anybody anymore.
而你一直领先我们一步
You've been ahead of us this whole time.
不过你猜怎么着 我现在在你前面了
But guess what? I'm ahead of you now.
你干什么我都知道
Your ass is mine.
你们FBI还是这么白痴
You guys are still idiots.
是吗
Yeah?
这是以前莱昂内尔史瑞克
This happens to be the former
排练表演的地方
rehearsal space for Lionel Shrike.
也是我第一次演出的地方
It's where I did my first show.
现在 如果你想知道你到底有多白痴
Now,if you wanna look like even bigger idiots,
不如打开它
why not open it?
罗兹警官 当你打开它时
And while you're doing it,Agent Rhodes,
你能表演给我看下
would you mind reenacting your look
什么叫傻货吗
of absolute befuddlement for me?
肯定会是我DVD一个很好的封面
It will make a wonderful cover for my DVD.
打开保险箱
Open the safe.
- 去吧 - 打开
- Go ahead. - Open it.
混蛋
What the hell?
什么
What?
把它给我
Give me that.
别
No.
别这样
No!
这是什么
What is this?
快退后
Get back!
谁不喜欢看精彩的魔术呢
Who doesn't love a good magic trick?
你们追了一次空箱子
They have you chasing empty safes again.
又一次啊 选错了方向
Once again,misdirection.
表演开始了 快走
The show is starting. Move out!
罗兹警官 我现在想问你的是
The question I'd be asking now,Agent Rhodes is,
"真的那个箱子呢"
"What happened to the real one?"
让开 叫他们让开
Clear! Clear 'em out!
快点 叫他们让开 让出路来
Come on. Move 'em out. Move 'em out of the way.
联邦调查局 让出路来
FBI! Give me a path!
让开 让开
Clear out! Clear out!
什么是魔术呢
What is magic?
魔术就是障眼法
Magic is deception.
但 是能让观众高兴
But deception designed to delight,
娱乐观众 鼓舞观众的把戏
to entertain,to inspire.
小心 让一让
Look out! Clear! Clear! Look out!
是一种信念
It is about belief.
信仰
Faith.
信任
Trust.
没有这些本质
Without those qualities,
魔术 作为一种艺术形式 就会永远消失
magic,as an art form,would no longer exist.
但是 如果这些本质
But what happens if these qualities
没有用在更好的目标上
are not used for their higher purpose?
那就会变成了欺骗 谎言
And instead they're used to cheat,lie.
如果是为了个人所需或贪念
For personal gain or for greed.
那就不再是魔术了
Then it's no longer magic.
那是犯罪
It's crime.
所以今晚 为了我们的最后一轮演出
So tonight,for our final act,
大家要帮我们矫正我们的行为
you're gonna help us set a few things right.
罗兹 这是怎么回事啊
What's going on here,Rhodes?
我也不知道
I don't know.
表演开始
Showtime.
看
Look!
他们在屋顶 我们走
There they are on the roof. Let's move!
快 快 快
Go,go,go!
- 迪伦 - 联邦调查局 让一让
- Dylan! - FBI,coming through!
你在这干嘛
What are you doing here?
他们走的方向是错的
They're going in the wrong direction
你知道的
and you know it.
罗兹 我需要全部人都来
Rhodes! I need all personnel now!
你要相信我 相信我一次也好
You need to trust me. Take your leap of faith.
等等
Wait.
我要跟她一起去
I'm going to go with her.
去吧 我在这里等你 我帮你看着
Go. I got your back. I'll be right here.
快去吧
Go ahead!
富勒 这次算你头上了
That's on you,Fuller.
快走 快 快 快
Let's go,let's go! Now,now,now!
丹尼尔
Daniel?
对我们来说…这危险时期
As our,let's call it,year of living dangerously
越走越近 并且也快到尾声了
comes to a close,in a rare moment of vulnerability,
我想为了我们的友谊
I'd like to express a sentiment
发表一下感受
to you about our relationship.
行啊
Okay.
嗯…当我第一次遇到你时 我就觉得你不是什么
Well,when I first met you,I thought you were kind of a
好货
dick.
然后呢
And?
没了 就这么多
No,that's it.
很好
That's very nice.
- 嗯 - 我很感动
- Yeah. - I'm touched.
嗯 这是我的心里话
Yeah. Just from the heart.
这样啊 我还没告诉你我哪里感动了
Well,I didn't tell you where I was touched.
天啊表演结束了我们怎么办啊
Oh,God. What are we gonna do when this is over?
我们还是我们啊
We're on our own.
我们的蓝图只说到表演结束之后
Our instructions run out after the show.
哪怕如果没有"正义之眼"
Even if there is no "Eye",
如果我们完成表演后
if we were completely played and we spend
在监狱呆20年 然后
the next 20 years in jail,then,
我想说…
I just want to say that...
我知道 我也是
I know. Me,too.
太多愁善感了
Little too sentimental for me.
他们在那
There they are!
抓住他们 快 快 快
Go grab 'em! Put 'em down! Go,go,go!
抓住他们
Grab 'em!
起来
Get up!
这是假的
What the hell?
靠
Shit!
你好 纽约
Hello,New York!
感谢魔术
Thank you for the magic.
感谢如此高清热涨的
And thank you for being such
观众们
an incredible and dedicated audience.
很不幸的是 就像所有美好的事物一样
Unfortunately,like all good things,
总会结束的
it must come to an end.
在今晚的表演开幕之际
So we would like to start our show tonight...
就已经要跟大家说再见了
By saying goodbye.
我们所想做的只是
All we wanted was to
给世界带来一次充满魔幻的表演
bring the world to a magic show.
由此带给世界一点点
And thereby bring a little magic
魔力
back to the world.
让开
Clear the way!
这对我们来说将会是 精彩的最后一次
This has been one hell of a ride for all of us.
但是就要和你们告别了
But it's time for us to disappear.
晚安 纽约
Good night,New York.
谢谢大家相信我们
And thank you for believing in us.
别走
Stop!
站住
Freeze!
别
No!
该死的
God damn it!
对不起
I'm sorry.
你说的对 唯有信念大过一切
You were right. It's bigger than all of us.
这次虽然我对了 但还是不开心
This is one time I'm not happy being right.
我猜就这样了吧
So I guess this is it.
是吗
Is it?
迪伦
Dylan!
迪伦 迪伦
Dylan! Dylan!
- 你看到了吗 - 什么
- You see that? - What?
真钱呢
Where's the real money?
你被捕了 举起手来 快
You're under arrest! Hands in the air! Now!
我是被陷害的
I've been framed.
我知道你是
I'm sure you were.
是啊 我可以证明我清白的
Yeah,but I can prove it.
我一直都可以
I always do.
就像之前我预测你被人耍一样简单
Just like I predicted that you'd play the fool.
我们不要再演戏了 行吗
Let's just drop the theatricality,all right?
这里又没有摄影机
The cameras aren't rolling in here.
伙计们 能给我点时间让我单独跟他谈谈吗
Fellas,can I have a few minutes with my friend here alone,please.
当然可以
Sure.
好了
All right.
我有消息可以作为交换
I got information to trade.
我相信应该没有问题吧
I believe that's how it's done. Huh?
行 如果你说的东西有价值的话
If it's of some value.
这铁笼子总能给一人深思熟虑的机会
These bars give a man time to think.
我非常肯定 他们如何做到的
And I'm pretty sure I know how they did it.
还记得第二次表演的兔子戏法吗
Remember the rabbit trick in the second show?
那个盒子一直都没空
The box was never empty.
那个房间也是
The room wasn't either.
进入仓库后
After gaining access to the warehouse,
骑士团移走了真正的保险箱
The Horsemen left the real safe
把整间房变成
and transformed the whole room
一个巨型兔子的盒子
into a giant rabbit box.
你过去查看时
You go charging in there,
认为保险箱已被运走了
thinking the safe was already gone.
喂
Hey!
喂 别走
Hey! Stop!
再次被骗了
Missing the trick. Again.
这也让你觉得
Which was to make you think
保险箱已经被偷
the safe had already been stolen,
所以你让你警卫离开了
so you'd drop your guard and leave.
然而 在你忙着玩动物气球时
Now,while you were busy playing with balloon animals,
已经有人闯进了仓库
someone was breaking into the warehouse.
谁
Who?
杰克·怀尔德
Jack Wilder.
真该死
Holy shit.
不 不可能 我亲眼看到他死在我眼前
No. No way. He died right in front of my eyes.
当然 除非 他没有死
Unless,of course,he didn't.
锁住了
It's locked.
你没听我说过吗
Weren't you listening?
没有什么能锁上我
Nothing's ever locked.
真棒 怀尔德先生 干的好
Well done,Mr. Wilder! Good work.
杰克 你现在是大男人了
You're a big boy now,Jack.
他从联邦调查局的车里逃出去的 对吗
He escaped in a standard FBI vehicle,right?
然后带你去桥上
Led you to the bridge.
这时 其他几个骑士也在桥上等着
Where the other Horsemen were waiting
还准备了一部完全相同的车
with an identical replacement car.
只要你失去
It only took a split second
视野一瞬间
for you to lose contact with it
调换一下
and make the switch.
当你爬进烧着的车时
When you crawled into that burning car,
非常英勇可以说是
quite heroically,I might add,
你冒着生命危险
you almost died trying to rescue
我猜应该是停尸间找来的一个尸体
what I assume was a cadaver from the morgue.
为什么要冒着这么危险 复杂的计划
Why go through such an elaborate and dangerous plan
就为陷害一个人
just to frame one guy?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们也不要偷来的钱
They never kept any of the money they took.
那部分也是我想不通的
Yeah,that's the part I haven't been able to put together yet.
但是我已经给了你足够重要的信息了
But I just gave you information that is substantially more important.
- 不 不一定 - 什么意思
- No. Not really. - What?
我终于有个机会能调查下莱昂内尔斯莱克的案子了
I finally got a chance to really look into Lionel Shrike.
他的东山再起 他的事故
His comeback attempt. His accident.
保险公司拒绝了他家庭的赔偿申诉
The insurer who denied the family's claim?
特雷斯勒 保险公司
Tressler Insurance.
而银行的笔记
The bank that carried the note?
是那个法国人的银行做的
Credit Republican of Paris.
巴黎信用合作行
Credit Republicain de Paris.
你这表情什么意思
What do you make of that?
每分钟都有混蛋出生
A sucker is born every minute.
这半夜2点 如果我们在
What if all this was just leading up to
中央公园被打劫了怎么办
us getting mugged in Central Park at 2:00 a.m.?
不会的 我跟你说 这儿就是我们要来的地方
No,I'm telling you,we're right where we need to be.
我们只是需要找到…
We just have to find...
那个
That?
莱昂内尔·史瑞克之树
The Lionel Shrike tree.
和树里的那张牌
And the card encased in glass.
我们现在怎么办
What do we do now?
太棒了
Oh,nice!
那么 我有个新的理论
So,here's my new theory.
传说中的荷鲁斯之眼是无处不在的
The legend is that the "Eye" is everywhere.
等待
Waiting
真正伟大的魔术师从无名鼠辈
for the truly great magicians to distinguish themselves
到大名鼎鼎
from the mediocre ones.
可能那个人曾会是你
Maybe that was you.
发自内心的想成为荷鲁斯之眼其中成员之一
Deep down inside you wanted nothing more
但是你却从未被邀请
than to be part of the "Eye," but you were never invited.
所以你试着扳倒他们 猜猜反而结果是怎么样的
So you try to destroy them. But instead what happens?
你惹怒了他们
You pissed them off.
那眼睛不是真实的
The Eye isn't real.
好吧 那你解释下 这背后到底都是谁
Okay,then,explain then. Who's behind all this?
肯定是个有妄想症的人
Somebody with an obsession.
- 特别较真的人 - 谁
- Meticulous. - Who?
一个已经准备好失去一切
Somebody prepared to sacrifice everything.
已经都准备过头了
Somebody so prepared to lose
以至于都没人发现他的可疑
that they wouldn't even be a suspect until the trick was done.
我不要详细资料 你就告诉我一个名字 是谁
I don't want a profile. I need a name. Who? Who?
我不知道是谁
I don't know who.
但是他们有能进入仓库的办法
But they had to have access to the warehouse
能够有机会安置那块镜子
to plant the mirrors.
一直在我和FBI之前一步
Always a step ahead of me. And the FBI.
让他们错过一次又一次
Got past them not once,not twice,but consistently.
除非是他们内部自己的…
Almost as if they were on the...
人
The inside.
是你
You.
为什么要这样
Why?
这问题问的真好 不是吗
That is the question,isn't it?
你说的对
You're right.
你不知道我等了多久
I can't tell you how long I've waited
才看到你这惊讶的脸庞
to see the look on your face.
你是谁
Who are you?
你到底想我怎么样
What do you want from me?
我想怎么样
What do I want?
我要你余生都在监狱里过完
I want you to spend the rest of your life in this cell,
你就一直盯着墙壁 想破脑袋
staring at four walls and wondering how you missed it.
想念你是怎么让自己变得这么自大的
How you let yourself be so blinded by your ego
以至于自己一直落后一步却还要
that you convinced yourself that you were one step ahead
一直强调自己领先一步
when you were always two steps behind.
迪伦
Dylan?
等一下
Wait a minute.
迪伦 什么情况
Dylan! How did this happen?
迪伦
Dylan!
为什么
Why?
哦 我的天
Oh,my God.
我都没猜到你来了
I did not see that coming.
不可能啊
That's impossible!
难以置信
No way.
真的很精彩
That was actually pretty good.
谢谢你
Thank you.
当我说 永远是那个房间里最聪明的人 的时候
When I said,"Always be the smartest guy in the room."
我们商量好了的
We were in agreement.
没问题
Okay. Right.
亨利
Henley.
我从没见她这样沉默
I've never seen her speechless.
我把这当成是赞赏的话了
I take that as a huge compliment.
嘿 太抱歉了 之前揍了你
Hey,man,I'm so sorry for kicking your ass. Really.
听好了 先说好啊
Hey,listen,for the record,
我可是个100%的信仰者
I have always been a 100% believer.
用来信仰魔法的精力
And the amount of energy I have expended to keep
如果用在一个点上
these infidels on point...
不用说了 梅里特 你合格了
Merritt,you're in.
感谢上帝
God bless.
来吧
Come.
真正的魔法就是把四股很强的力量
The real magic is taking four strong solo acts
汇集到一起
and making them all work together.
这也正是你们所做的
And that's exactly what you did.
那么 欢迎加入
So welcome.
欢迎加入正义之眼
Welcome to the Eye.
(大型逃脱魔术成了史莱克一生最后一个魔术)
确实有联系这几个
It was all connected.
法国银行 特雷斯特保险公司
Credit Republican. Tressler Insurance.
你好
Bonjour
以及埃尔克霍恩
And Elkhorn?
那跟斯莱克有什么关系
What's the connection to Shrike?
埃尔克霍恩是做保险柜起家的
Elkhorn started as a safe manufacturer.
他们用廉价的铁料
They used cheap steel.
缺边减料的
They cut corners.
当斯莱克沉入河底的时候保险柜变形了
When he got to the bottom of the river,the safe warped.
然后他被困了
And he was trapped.
他是你的父亲
He was your father.
那天早上 表演开始之前 一切都如同昨天
The morning before the show didn't feel like any other day.
当我父亲说他要去工作的时候 他没看出来我不想他离开
When my father said he had to go to work,he could see that I didn't want him to leave.
所以他给了我他的表 让我数到他回来
So he gave me his watch,and he told me to count the seconds until he came back.
之后他的表就再也没能停下来
I have never let his watch stop since then.
从那一刻起
And from that moment on,
我给自己制定了一个角色
I created a persona.
我开始计划 详细的部署每个细节
I planned. I worked out every detail.
但是有一样东西我没能预料到
But the one thing that I couldn't imagine happening
那就是你
was you.
我知道你的逻辑总结能力
And I know that the logical conclusion for you
能带你找到这个案子的答案
is to take this case to its resolution.
然后你会把我带走
And for you to turn me in.
是的
Yeah.
但是此刻我对逻辑和答案怎么理解
But you know how I feel about resolution and logic.
你也知道
And you also know
我认为有一些事还是作为秘密最好
that I think some things are best left unexplained.
又有一个秘密可以锁住了
One more secret to lock away.
近一点
Come in close.
再近点
Closer.
因为现在你知道了我们的秘密
Because now you know our secret.
我们可能在任何一个地方 监视你
We could be anywhere. Watching you.
我们在寻找能帮助我们下个演出的人
We're looking for someone to help us with our next trick.
数到三 睁开你的双眼
On the count of three,open your eyes
然后告诉我 你看到什么
and tell me what you see.
一
One.
二
Two...
快 停下来 拜托了
Please,stop,stop,stop.
好了 快点停下来 不停我跳车了
All right,stop the van. Stop the van. I'm gonna jump out of the van.
哦 谢天谢地
Oh,thank God.
我们在哪
Where are we?
好吧 又是个鸟不拉屎的地方
Great,another shit hole.
好了 就感受下这儿吧
Okay,feeling it.
我感到疲劳 饥饿 骨架都散了
I'm exhausted,and hungry,and cranky.
瞧瞧这儿啊
Check out this place.
- 你要带我们去哪里 - 能不能不要是垃圾场
- Where'd you bring us? - Was there no landfill where we were?
这地方真酷
This place is awesome.
这就是我们的新地方吗
Is this our new gear?
最好别 这地方像拼起来的一样
There'd better not be,like,matching jumpsuits in there.
你知道我不爱这种地方
You know I don't wear spandex.
- 锁起来的 - 各位 牌呢
- It's Locked. - Guys,the cards.
- 什么牌 - "什么牌"是什么意思
- What card? - What do you mean, "what card"?
好吧
Okay.